<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>glenn youngkin on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in glenn youngkin on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>glenn youngkin bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/bio/</guid>
      <description>Gov. ‍Glenn Youngkin bio ‍Glenn Youngkin is a homegrown Virginian who grew up in Richmond and Virginia Beach. As his father changed jobs, Governor-Elect Youngkin learned that moving around didn’t equal moving up – nothing was handed to him. From his first job washing dishes and frying eggs at a diner in Virginia Beach, he embraced hard work and responsibility to help his family when his father lost his job. His determination to succeed earned him multiple high school basketball honors in Virginia and an athletic scholarship to college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winsome Sears</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/winsome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/winsome/</guid>
      <description>About Lieutenant Governor Winsome Earle-Sears Winsome Earle-Sears, a native of Kingston, Jamaica, immigrated to the United States at the age of six. She is proud to have served in the United States Marine Corps. In addition to her various appointments, she has served as the Vice President of the Virginia State Board of Education; and as a presidential appointee to the US Census Bureau, as co-chair of the African American Committee; and the Advisory Committee on Women Veterans to the Secretary of Veterans Affairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kay James </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/james/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/james/</guid>
      <description>About Kay Coles James The Honorable Kay Coles James was born in Portsmouth, Virginia, and raised in her early years in Richmond’s housing projects to a single mother in the segregated South. Secretary James was one of the first children to take part in a historic experiment to desegregate Virginia’s all-white schools and later graduated from Hampton University.
She most recently served as the President of the Heritage Foundation, a prominent think tank in Washington, D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Miyares</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/jason/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/jason/</guid>
      <description>About the Attorney General Jason Miyares Attorney General Jason Miyares&amp;rsquo; story doesn&amp;rsquo;t start in Virginia Beach, Virginia, but in Havana, Cuba when his mother, Miriam Miyares, fled communist Cuba, penniless and homeless. She taught Jason a love for freedom, democracy, and that America is indeed the “last best hope on earth.” A product of Virginia public schools, Jason graduated with a Bachelor’s in Business Administration from James Madison University and received his J.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
