<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>John Boozman on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/</link>
    <description>Recent content in John Boozman on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>John Boozman biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/bio/</guid>
      <description>John Boozman biograph John Boozman is Arkansas’s senior U.S. Senator and the dean of the state’s Congressional delegation.
A fifth-generation Arkansan, John was raised in Fort Smith and graduated from Northside High School. He went on to play football for the University of Arkansas Razorbacks while completing his pre-optometry requirements. He graduated from the Southern College of Optometry in 1977 and entered private practice that same year co-founding a family business with his brother that would ultimately become a major provider of eye care to Northwest Arkansas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Boozman political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/political/</guid>
      <description>John&amp;rsquo;s political view Issues John Boozman, a successful businessman and life-long resident of Arkansas, has represented Arkansas in the United States Senate for six years, establishing a record as a strong supporter of the values and principles that Arkansans hold dearly. He will continue this same commitment to the people of the Natural State in his second term as your United States Senator.
Winning the War on Terror Requires Confronting Radical Islam If anyone embodies a twisted view of radical Islam, it is the Islamic State (ISIS) terror organization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
