<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>senator mark kelly contact phone on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/tags/senator-mark-kelly-contact-phone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in senator mark kelly contact phone on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/tags/senator-mark-kelly-contact-phone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mark Kelly</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/mark-kelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/mark-kelly/</guid>
      <description>Mark Kelly has served his country as a U.S. Navy combat pilot, a NASA astronaut, and now as a U.S. Senator for Arizona. He is an independent leader who came to the Senate to serve Arizona’s working families, not corporate special interests.
As the son of two police officers, Senator Kelly learned the value of public service at an early age. He attended public schools from elementary school all the way through graduate school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Kelly Political Views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/mark-kelly/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/mark-kelly/political/</guid>
      <description>Health Care As a cancer survivor and the husband of Gabby Giffords, who was nearly killed in a shooting and owes her life to quality medical care, Mark has a deep appreciation for the importance of health care and coverage that you can rely on. Mark knows that he and Gabby were fortunate to have good insurance that covered the lifesaving care they needed, but that many Arizona families lack affordable health coverage.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
