<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Larry Hogan on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Larry Hogan on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Larry Hogan bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/bio/</guid>
      <description>About Governor Lawrence J. Hogan Governor Lawrence J. Hogan, Jr. was sworn in as the 62nd governor of the State of Maryland on January 21, 2015. In 2018, he was overwhelmingly re-elected to a second four-year term, receiving the most votes of any Maryland gubernatorial candidate and becoming only the second Republican governor to be re-elected in the 242-year history of the state.
In his first inaugural address, Governor Hogan reminded citizens of Maryland’s history as a state of middle temperament and pledged to advance the best ideas, regardless of which side of the political aisle they come from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yumi Hogan</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/bio/</guid>
      <description>Maryland’s First Lady Yumi Hogan Maryland’s First Lady, Yumi Hogan, is the first Korean American First Lady in the United States and the first Asian American First Lady of Maryland. She is the youngest of eight children and grew up on a farm in the countryside of South Korea. Mrs. Hogan is a first-generation Korean American, the mother of three daughters, and has four grandchildren.
Mrs. Hogan is an accomplished artist and adjunct professor at Maryland Institute College of Art.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
