<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>governors on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/tags/governors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in governors on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:05:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/tags/governors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Ron DeSantis for President of the United States</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:05:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-president/</guid>
      <description>Meet Ron DeSantis Ron DeSantis, a native Floridian with blue-collar roots, grew up in Dunedin under the care of his nurse mother and cable box installer father. He attended Dunedin High School before earning his way through Yale University, where he served as captain of the varsity baseball team. Ron&amp;rsquo;s dedication to education continued as he graduated with honors from Harvard Law School and earned a commission as a JAG officer in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Governor DeSantis Unveils Legislation to Address Illegal Immigration Threats in Florida</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/gov-ron-desantis-new-legislative-proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 10:05:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/gov-ron-desantis-new-legislative-proposal/</guid>
      <description>Governor Ron DeSantis of Florida has announced an extensive legislative proposal aimed at addressing illegal immigration threats in the state. The proposal seeks to address issues caused by the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s failure to secure the US border. The legislation includes measures such as increasing penalties for human smuggling, strengthening detention statutes for illegal aliens, mandating the use of E-Verify, enhancing penalties for document falsification, and prohibiting local governments from issuing ID cards to people who are unlawfully in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Laura Kelly for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/laura-kelly-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:02:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/laura-kelly-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Laura Kelly for Kansas governor Governor Laura Kelly has brought Democrats and Republicans together to balance the budget, fully fund our schools, and fight for a tax cut for all Kansans. Laura will always put what’s best for Kansas ahead of party politics.
Meet Laura Kelly Governor Laura Kelly brings together both parties to get things done for Kansas. Laura has brought jobs, businesses, opportunities, and record economic success to Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Nellie Gorbea for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/nellie-gorbea-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 12:04:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/nellie-gorbea-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Nellie Gorbea for Rhode Island governor Rhode Island Secretary of State Nellie M. Gorbea was re-elected in 2018 to serve Rhode Island for a second term and continue making government work for people. She made history when she was sworn in on January 6, 2015, becoming the first Hispanic elected to statewide office in New England. Since then, she has rapidly emerged on the national scene as a leader who is taking on some of the toughest issues and getting results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Michelle Lujan Grisham for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/michelle-lujan-grisham-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 11:06:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/michelle-lujan-grisham-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Michelle Lujan Grisham for New Mexico governor Michelle Lujan Grisham is the 32nd Governor of New Mexico and was the first Democratic Hispanic woman to serve as Governor of a U.S. state. As a 12th-generation New Mexican, she has dedicated her life to serving her community while fighting for families and building an economy that works for all New Mexicans.
After graduating from the University of New Mexico’s law school, Governor Lujan Grisham worked to provide free legal services for seniors with the state bar’s lawyer referral program for the elderly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Brenda Siegel  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/brenda-siegel-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:09:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/brenda-siegel-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Brenda Siegel for governor About Brenda Brenda was born in Brattleboro, Vermont. She graduated from Brattleboro Union High School and after college, she worked as a teacher, political intern, and choreographer. In 2002, she became a single mom and decided to open a small business and raise her child in Vermont near her own family. Brenda’s father was a commercial photographer and small business owner. Her mother was a dancer and is an American Sign language interpreter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Bob Stefanowski  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/bob-stefanowski-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/bob-stefanowski-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Bob Stefanowski for governor Bob Stefanowski grew up in a family like many of us are blessed to have.
His roots are on Dixwell Avenue in New Haven, where his family lived in a three-family home. Having his grandparents on the first floor meant lots of stories about how his family came to America through Ellis Island from Poland. Bob’s great grandmother shucked oysters in Fair Haven, he’s always been proud to have a family history in some of the world’s finest oysters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tim Michels  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-michels-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-michels-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Tim Michels for governor Born and raised in Brownsville, Tim Michels, endorsed by President Trump, is a conservative outsider who has a plan to put Wisconsin on the right track.
At the age of nine, Tim’s dad handed him a shovel and taught him how to dig trenches, while his mom taught him how to drive trucks. After graduating from Lomira High School in Dodge County, he attended Saint Norbert College in Green Bay, where he was active in ROTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kari Lake  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kari-lake-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kari-lake-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kari Lake for governor Kari Lake, the former anchor for Fox 10 News in Phoenix, became a symbol of truth in journalism when she walked away from the mainstream media despite being number one in the ratings for more than two decades.
Now she&amp;rsquo;s running for Governor of Arizona on a platform of common sense conservatism dedicated to individual liberties, low taxes, limited regulation, and protecting Arizona&amp;rsquo;s great Western heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Katie Hobbs for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/katie-hobbs-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/katie-hobbs-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Katie Hobbs for governor Born and raised in the Grand Canyon State, Katie Hobbs has dedicated her life to listening to her community and helping solve difficult challenges for the people of Arizona. A fearless advocate for Arizona, Katie is ready to bring transparency and accountability to the Governor’s office and deliver real results for all of us.
Born and raised in Arizona, Katie learned the value of service at an early age from her parents and her church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Chris Jones  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/chris-jones-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 11:07:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/chris-jones-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Chris Jones for governor As a son of two preachers, I was raised with a strong sense of faith. This faith has never collided with my love for science — in fact, it only made it grow stronger. I attended Morehouse College on a NASA Scholarship, for physics and math, then studied at MIT to become a nuclear engineer and earn a Ph.D. in urban planning. I was blessed to run the Arkansas Regional Innovation Hub, which provided the tools and technology Arkansans needed to build businesses and create jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Deidre DeJear  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/deidre-dejear-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 11:07:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/deidre-dejear-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Deidre DeJear for governor Iowans want someone to get to work for them. Deidre has dedicated her life to serving her community and that is what she will do as Governor starting on Day One.
Deidre was born in Jackson, Mississippi, and as a child moved with her family to Oklahoma. At eight years old, Deidre’s mother passed away shortly after giving birth to her younger sister. Overcoming this adversity at such a young age and seeing her dad be present for her and her siblings shaped who Deidre is today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kevin Stitt for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kevin-stitt-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 11:07:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kevin-stitt-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kevin Stitt for governor Governor Kevin Stitt is leading Oklahoma with a vision to become Top Ten in job growth, infrastructure, education and more.
Stitt is an entrepreneur who founded Gateway Mortgage in 2000 in Tulsa, Oklahoma. Starting with only $1,000 and a computer, he grew Gateway Mortgage into a nationwide mortgage company operating in more than 40 states and servicing more than $20 billion in residential mortgages.
In 2018, he led Gateway through a merger and established Gateway First Bank, which today is one of Oklahoma’s 10 largest banks with over $2 billion in assets, 160 mortgage centers across the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Stacey Abrams  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/stacey-abrams-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:07:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/stacey-abrams-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Stacey Abrams for governor Stacey Abrams grew up in Gulfport, Mississippi, one of six children whose parents had three tenets: go to church, go to school, and take care of each other. Her father, a shipyard worker, and mother, a college librarian, faced financial hardships of their own, yet they taught their children the value of service to others. No matter how much they struggled to make ends meet, Stacey and her siblings were taught that someone always had less and that it was their job to serve that person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kay Ivey  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kay-ivey-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kay-ivey-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kay Ivey for governor When Kay Ivey was first sworn-in as the 54th Governor of the State of Alabama in April 2017, she got right to work cleaning up Montgomery and restoring the people’s trust in government. That’s because Kay is a conservative fighter, whose life has prepared her to lead our state towards prosperity and opportunity for every Alabamian.
She grew up working on the family farm in Wilcox County.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Maura Healey for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/maura-healey-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/maura-healey-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Maura Healey for governor Maura Healey has spent her career standing up for the people of Massachusetts and pursuing justice and equality. She’s running for Governor to bring people together and expand economic opportunities for everyone in Massachusetts.
Maura has deep roots in Massachusetts. Her parents both grew up in Newburyport. Her maternal grandparents met in Gloucester, where her grandfather worked on the fishing docks and her grandmother, whose ancestors settled on the Parker River in Newbury in 1636, went to nursing school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Carol Blood for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/carol-blood-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/carol-blood-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Carol Blood for governor My name is Carol Blood. I’m a Nebraskan, born and raised. I was born in McCook, Nebraska, raised in rural Adams County, Nebraska and raised my family in Sarpy County, Nebraska. My husband Joe and I have been married for 34 years and are blessed with three adult children and 10 grandchildren.
I love my community and have been an active volunteer and community advocate for decades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kathy Hochul for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kathy-hochul-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kathy-hochul-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kathy Hochul for governor Kathy Hochul is the 57th Governor of New York. A lifelong New Yorker, she was born and raised in a blue-collar Irish Catholic family in Buffalo that instilled a deep passion for public service and activism. She continued that fighting spirit as a student organizer, as a young attorney and aide to Sen. Daniel Patrick Moynihan, and then as a member of her Town Board, Erie County Clerk, member of Congress, lieutenant governor, and now as governor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mark Gordon for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/mark-gordon-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/mark-gordon-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Mark Gordon for governor Mark Gordon was elected Wyoming’s 33rd Governor, on Nov. 6, 2018. He was sworn into office on January 7, 2019.
Mark Gordon grew up on the family ranch in Wyoming where he learned the values of hard work and integrity and the importance of working together. As Governor, he brings those values to the table, maintaining his commitment to a Wyoming where its citizens can pursue their dreams while the state retains its unique character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Joe Lombardo  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/joe-lombardo-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:06:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/joe-lombardo-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Joe Lombardo for governor Joe is Running for Governor to Save Nevada
Joe Lombardo began his service to others in the United States Army and served bravely in the Army, National Guard, and Army Reserve - protecting Americans both domestically and abroad. After his service to his country, Joe dedicated himself to protecting our communities – serving in law enforcement over the last 30 years.
Joe quickly rose through the ranks of the Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department (LVMPD) and, after 26 years on the force, was elected as Sheriff of Clark County, Nevada in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mike DeWine  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/mike-dewine-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:03:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/mike-dewine-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Mike DeWine for governor Mike DeWine’s story is a true Ohio story. Growing up in Yellow Springs, Mike and Fran (Struewing) met in the first grade and married while students at Miami University. They’ve been blessed with eight children and 26 grandchildren. Family is at the core of everything Mike DeWine does, and that’s why he has devoted his life to fighting for Ohio’s families.
Guided by his family and faith, Mike has governed as a compassionate conservative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Nan Whaley  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/nan-whaley-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:03:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/nan-whaley-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Nan Whaley for governor Nan grew up in a small town in Indiana. She learned the values of hard work, strength, and resilience from her dad, a union autoworker who lost his job but never lost his dignity, and her mom, who went to work at the laundromat behind their house to help make ends meet.
Back then, Ohio was where people went for opportunity, so she attended the University of Dayton, becoming the first person in her family to graduate from college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jamie Smith for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/jamie-smith-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:03:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/jamie-smith-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Jamie Smith for governor Jamie serves as Minority Leader in the South Dakota House of Representatives, where he has delivered bipartisan solutions for the people of South Dakota. Jamie believes we are strongest when we work together to get things done.
Jamie is a lifelong South Dakotan. A realtor and former educator, Jamie isn’t a career politician, and he understands the needs of all South Dakotans. Every day, Jamie rolls up his sleeves to bring people together on the big issues South Dakotans face: affordable housing, high-quality education and healthcare, and an economy that works for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kristi Noem for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kristi-noem-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kristi-noem-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kristi Noem for South Dakota governor Kristi Noem is a wife, mother, grandmother, rancher, farmer, small business owner, and New York Times bestselling author of &amp;ldquo;Not My First Rodeo: Lessons from the Heartland.&amp;rdquo;
Governor Kristi Noem’s political career began with her 2006 election to the South Dakota State Legislature followed by her move to the United States House of Representatives and finally a return to Pierre as the state’s first female Governor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jared Polis for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/jared-polis-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/jared-polis-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Jared Polis for governor Governor Polis is a hard-working Coloradan who has run successful businesses, delivered better education opportunities for our kids and is now serving as Colorado’s 43rd Governor. Under his leadership, Colorado is working to become one of the most family-friendly states while topping the list of strongest state economies in the country.
Since taking office in 2019, Governor Polis has delivered on the top priorities he committed to tackle for Colordans – lowering the cost of childcare and getting more kids in free, full-day kindergarten, reducing the cost of healthcare, accelerating our fight against climate change and lowering taxes for hard-working families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gretchen Whitmer for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/gretchen-whitmer-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/gretchen-whitmer-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Gretchen Whitmer for governor Governor Gretchen Whitmer was inaugurated as the 49th governor of Michigan on January 1, 2019. Her career includes serving in the Michigan State House, as the first woman Senate Democratic Leader, and prosecutor for Ingham County, fighting for survivors’ rights and to reform how sexual assault cases are handled. Inspired by her service and family, she is dedicated to improving the lives of all Michiganders.
Gov. Whitmer has been a lifelong resident of Michigan, receiving both a BA and JD from Michigan State University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Lou Leon Guerrero  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/lou-leon-guerrero-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/lou-leon-guerrero-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Lou Leon Guerrero for governor The Honorable Lourdes “Lou” Aflague Leon Guerrero is the ninth Governor of Guam. She is the first female governor of the territory and is a registered nurse, a businesswoman, a policymaker, a mother, and a grandmother.
Since taking office in January 2019, she’s nearly eliminated GovGuam’s deficit from $83 million to $1.5 million. Additionally, she increased the minimum wage, legalized cannabis, ended two federal receiverships, and paid millions in war reparations owed to Guam’s WWII survivors with adjudicated claims.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> les gara  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/les-gara-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/les-gara-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>les gara for governor Like many Alaskans, Les grew up without wealth or privilege. When he was six, a robber broke into his father’s office. He was working late and the robber killed him. Les grew up in foster homes, where he lived for twelve years until he graduated high school. While Les worked from grade school through law school, he had good public schools and the opportunity to succeed. That’s what everyone deserves: an equal right to opportunity, liberty and justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Steve Sisolak  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/steve-sisolak-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/steve-sisolak-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Steve Sisolak for governor Steve Sisolak was born into a midwest working-class family. His parents Ed and Mary worked hard to provide for their three children and Steve inherited their blue-collar ethic, working full-time to put himself through college at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. Steve then enrolled in UNLV’s Graduate Studies Program, where he received a master’s degree in 1978.
Steve put down roots in Las Vegas, built his own communications business while raising his two daughters on his own as a single father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> stephen heidt for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/stephen-heidt-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/stephen-heidt-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>stephen heidt for governor I&amp;rsquo;m not a career politician, but I know enough about right and wrong to make a difference in our great state.
EDUCATION AND LEADERSHIP As a 4th generation Idahoan who grew up in a small agricultural community a few miles south of Preston, Idaho. I had a modest upbringing and started working at the dairy down the street from my house at age 10. I was at work by 4:00 a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Brad Little for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/brad-little-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/brad-little-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Brad Little for governor Brad Little is Idaho’s 33rd Governor, leading the people of Idaho through the most prosperous time in state history! A lifelong conservative, Governor Little’s first term is marked by historic tax relief, unparalleled red tape reduction, extraordinary economic growth, and unprecedented investments in education to ensure a strong workforce for years to come.
Governor Little is committed to continuing to lead Idaho with his goal for Idaho in mind – to make Idaho the place where we all can have the opportunity to thrive, where our children and grandchildren choose to stay, and for the ones who have left to choose to return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Paul LePage for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/paul-lepaige-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/paul-lepaige-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Paul LePage for governor Paul was born and raised in Lewiston, Maine. The oldest son of eighteen children in an impoverished, dysfunctional family, Paul left home at the age of eleven to escape severe domestic violence.
He was homeless and living on the streets. He slept anywhere he could and earned as much as he could shining shoes and doing odd jobs. A Franco-American kid, a group then considered a minority in Maine and who had been aggressively targeted several years before in Maine by the Ku Klux Klan, life presented other problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Janet Trafton Mills for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/janet-mills-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/janet-mills-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Janet Trafton Mills for governor Janet Mills is Maine through and through – and no one loves this state or believes in its people more than she does. That’s why she has always fought for Maine people and always will. She wants to keep moving Maine forward.
Born and raised in rural Maine, Janet is the granddaughter of potato farmers from Aroostook County and the daughter of a World War II veteran and public school teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gavin Newsom for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/gavin-newsom-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 12:06:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/gavin-newsom-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gavin Newsom for governor Gavin Christopher Newsom (born October 10, 1967) is an American politician and businessman serving as the 40th governor of California since January 2019. A member of the Democratic Party, he served as the 49th lieutenant governor of California from 2011 to 2019 and as the 42nd mayor of San Francisco from 2004 to 2011. Newsom attended Redwood High School and graduated from Santa Clara University. After graduation, he founded the PlumpJack wine store with family friend Gordon Getty as an investor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Brian dahle for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/brian-dahle-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:07:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/brian-dahle-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Brian dahlefor California governor Senator Brian Dahle is a voice for public safety, lowering taxes, and reducing homelessness. He opposes onerous government regulations that are driving up the cost of living forcing many to leave California and businesses to shutter their doors.
A longtime advocate of building a better business climate in California, Brian Dahle was the California Chamber of Commerce’s top-rated senator for pro-business votes in 2021 and has a 100 percent rating from the National Federation of Independent Business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Scott Jensen for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/scott-jensen-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:04:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/scott-jensen-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Scott Jensen for Minnesota governor Lifelong Minnesotan Born and raised in Sleepy Eye, Minnesota, Dr. Scott Jensen graduated valedictorian of his 1973 high school class. He attended the University of Minnesota obtaining an undergraduate degree in physiology, magna cum laude, and then attended Luther Theological Seminary seeking answers to life‘s biggest questions. The seminary proved to be an ideal setting for profound decision making as he made two life-changing decisions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tim Walz for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-walz-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-walz-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Tim Walzfor Minnesota governor Tim’s career has been defined by public service, from serving in the National Guard for 24 years, to serving our students as a high school teacher and football coach, to serving our state as a Congressman, and now as Minnesota’s 41st Governor.
Tim’s parents, Jim and Darlene, instilled in him the values that continue to guide his commitment to the common good and selfless service. Summers working on his family’s farm reinforced these lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Doug Mastriano for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/doug-mastrian-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/doug-mastrian-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Doug Mastrianofor Pennsylvania governor Doug Mastriano is a combat veteran and the son of a career US Navy man. He is an Eagle Scout and worked as a paperboy, janitor, security guard, short-order cook, pizza delivery person and dishwasher. Doug was commissioned in the U.S. Army in 1986 and served on the Iron Curtain with the 2nd Armored Cavalry Regiment in West Germany. While serving along the East German and Czechoslovakian borders, he witnessed the end of the Cold War and thereafter deployed to Iraq for Operation Desert Storm (1991) to liberate Kuwait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Josh Shapiro for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/josh-shapiro-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/josh-shapiro-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Josh Shapiro for governor Throughout his career as a public servant, Josh Shapiro has taken on the status quo, brought people together to solve tough problems, and delivered results for the people of Pennsylvania. Since 2017, he has served as the People’s Attorney General, working every day to stand up to powerful institutions and protect Pennsylvanians’ rights. Now, Josh is running to be Pennsylvania’s next Governor — to move our Commonwealth forward and tackle our biggest challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jason Martin  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/jason-martin-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/jason-martin-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Jason Martin for governor As a father, doctor, and business owner Jason Martin has dedicated his life to improving the lives and livelihoods of everyday Tennesseans.
Dr. Jason Martin was raised in Southern Alabama in a place much like many of our small communities in Tennessee. He was a latch key kid and his parents and step-parents worked hard every single day. While they labored hard to provide for Jason, his many aunts, uncles, and grandparents helped to raise him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Greg Abbott  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/greg-abbott-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/greg-abbott-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Greg Abbott for governor Named “Best Governor in the Nation” in his current second term, Governor Greg Abbott continues to build on his record as a strong conservative leader who fights to preserve Texas values and ensure the Lone Star State remains the best place to raise a family, build a business, and create greater opportunity for all.
Texas works when Texans work Under Governor Abbott’s strong stewardship, the Texas economy has expanded to nearly $2 trillion as the Lone Star State continues to break all records for total jobs, with more Texans working than at any point in the state’s history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ron DeSantis for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 10:05:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Ron DeSantis is the 46th Governor of Florida.
A native Floridian with blue-collar roots, Ron attended Dunedin High School and worked his way through Yale University, where he graduated with honors and was the captain of the varsity baseball team. He also graduated with honors from Harvard Law School. While at Harvard, he earned a commission in the U.S. Navy as a JAG officer. During his active-duty service, Ron deployed to Iraq as an adviser to a U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
