<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Incomes on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/income/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Incomes on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/income/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> How Is My Credit Score Calculated?</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/income/understanding-credit-scores/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/income/understanding-credit-scores/</guid>
      <description>A credit score helps lenders determine how likely you are to pay back what you owe. A good score can help you qualify for better interest rates on credit cards, car loans or a mortgage. Your credit score is based on factors that include payment history, your debt load and how long you’ve used credit. Reviewing your credit report regularly is the first step to improving your credit score. Having a good credit score is one of the keys to financial freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> IRS Stimulus Checks </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/income/stimulus-checks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/income/stimulus-checks/</guid>
      <description>Million of Americans received a first round of stimulus checks starting in April after the country shutdown and the economy took a hit. This guide will cover who qualifies for the first round of stimulus checks, who does not qualify for one, and any special requirements there may be in order to receive one.
Using the IRS Stimulus Check Portal The IRS Stimulus Check Portal is an online tool you can use to check on the status of your stimulus check, enter your direct deposit information, and confirm your mailing address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Senator Role to the people</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/income/senators-roles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/income/senators-roles/</guid>
      <description>the majority of individuals don’t know the role their senators play in the senate. True, we tend to assume that the congressman’s mandate is to foresee projects in the government. However, what the majority don’t know is that every one of them has employees whose work is to deliver constituent service. The service is specially designed to help people with concrete issues- usually involving a federal agency.
In most cases, the senate works on sorting out issues around Internal Revenue Service problems, mortgage issues, social security problems, immigration requests, and veterans’ benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus Relief</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/income/covid-19-relief/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/income/covid-19-relief/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of programs available to Americans to help assist them throughout the coronavirus (COVID-19) pandemic.
Stimulus Checks &amp;amp; Financial Assistance Stimulus checks for American families Stimulus checks to help ease the economic strain caused by the coronavirus (COVID-19) crisis will be sent to the vast majority of Americans in the coming days and weeks. Most Americans will not need to do anything in order to receive their checks while some will be required to update their information before getting a check.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
