<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Current Legislative bills introduced on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/bills/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Current Legislative bills introduced on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:02:29 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/bills/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Consolidated Appropriations Act, 2023</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr2617/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr2617/</guid>
      <description>The bill being discussed is an appropriations bill that covers a range of policy areas and provides funding to federal agencies for the remainder of the fiscal year 2023. It includes the 12 regular appropriations bills that fund federal agencies, such as the Department of Defense, Department of Homeland Security, and Department of Labor, Health and Human Services, and Education. The bill also provides supplemental appropriations for disaster relief and to support Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Energy Cybersecurity University Leadership Act of 2023</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr302/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr302/</guid>
      <description>The Energy Cybersecurity University Leadership Act of 2023 is a bill that aims to support the development of a next-generation energy-specific cybersecurity workforce. The bill directs the Secretary of Energy to provide financial assistance to graduate students and postdoctoral researchers pursuing certain courses of study related to cybersecurity and energy infrastructure. The assistance will be provided on a competitive basis in the form of scholarships, fellowships, and research and development projects at institutions of higher education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Social Security Fairness Act of 2023</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr82/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr82/</guid>
      <description>H.R. 82 - Social Security Fairness Act of 2023
The &amp;ldquo;Social Security Fairness Act of 2023,&amp;rdquo; designated as H.R. 82 in the 118th Congress, was introduced on January 9, 2023, by Mr. Graves of Louisiana and co-sponsored by several other representatives. This bill aims to make significant changes to the Social Security system by addressing two key provisions: the Government Pension Offset (GPO) and the Windfall Elimination Provision (WEP). Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed breakdown of the bill&amp;rsquo;s provisions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Denouncing the horrors of socialism</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hconres9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hconres9/</guid>
      <description>The concurrent resolution denounces the horrors of socialism. The resolution states that socialist ideology results in the concentration of power which has frequently led to the establishment of communist regimes, totalitarian rule, and brutal dictatorships. The resolution highlights the fact that many of the worst crimes in history have been committed by socialist ideologues, including Vladimir Lenin, Joseph Stalin, Mao Zedong, Fidel Castro, and others. The resolution also mentions the devastating consequences of the implementation of socialism in various countries, such as the Bolshevik Revolution, the USSR gulags, the famine and devastation caused by the Great Leap Forward in China, the killing fields in Cambodia, and the current state of Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Chinese Surveillance Balloon Incident Sparks Condemnation</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hres104/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hres104/</guid>
      <description>This Resolution concerns a high-altitude surveillance balloon belonging to the People’s Republic of China (PRC) that was tracked by the Department of Defense over United States territory on February 2, 2023. It was later revealed that the balloon was first tracked by North American Aerospace Defense Command (NORAD) on January 28, 2023. The Secretary of Defense has stated that the balloon was being used by the PRC for surveillance of strategic sites in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Born-Alive Abortion Survivors Protection Act</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr26/</guid>
      <description>Born-Alive Abortion Survivors Protection Act This bill establishes requirements for the degree of care a health care practitioner must provide in the case of a child born alive following an abortion or attempted abortion.
Specifically, a health care practitioner who is present must
exercise the same degree of care as would reasonably be provided to any other child born alive at the same gestational age, and ensure the child is immediately admitted to a hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FairTax Act of 2023</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr25/</guid>
      <description>This bill imposes a national sales tax on the use or consumption in the United States of taxable property or services in lieu of the current income taxes, payroll taxes, and estate and gift taxes. The rate of the sales tax will be 23% in 2025, with adjustments to the rate in subsequent years. There are exemptions from the tax for used and intangible property; for property or services purchased for business, export, or investment purposes; and for state government functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Floyd Justice in Policing Act of 2021</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr1280/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr1280/</guid>
      <description>The bill under discussion aims to address a wide range of issues and policies related to policing practices and law enforcement accountability. It aims to increase accountability for law enforcement misconduct and enhance transparency and data collection. The bill also aims to establish best practices and training requirements for law enforcement officers.
One of the key provisions of the bill is to enhance existing enforcement mechanisms to remedy violations by law enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
