<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>florida on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/categories/florida/</link>
    <description>Recent content in florida on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:05:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/categories/florida/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Ron DeSantis for President of the United States</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:05:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-president/</guid>
      <description>Meet Ron DeSantis Ron DeSantis, a native Floridian with blue-collar roots, grew up in Dunedin under the care of his nurse mother and cable box installer father. He attended Dunedin High School before earning his way through Yale University, where he served as captain of the varsity baseball team. Ron&amp;rsquo;s dedication to education continued as he graduated with honors from Harvard Law School and earned a commission as a JAG officer in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Governor DeSantis Unveils Legislation to Address Illegal Immigration Threats in Florida</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/gov-ron-desantis-new-legislative-proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 10:05:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/gov-ron-desantis-new-legislative-proposal/</guid>
      <description>Governor Ron DeSantis of Florida has announced an extensive legislative proposal aimed at addressing illegal immigration threats in the state. The proposal seeks to address issues caused by the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s failure to secure the US border. The legislation includes measures such as increasing penalties for human smuggling, strengthening detention statutes for illegal aliens, mandating the use of E-Verify, enhancing penalties for document falsification, and prohibiting local governments from issuing ID cards to people who are unlawfully in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ron DeSantis for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 10:05:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Ron DeSantis is the 46th Governor of Florida.
A native Floridian with blue-collar roots, Ron attended Dunedin High School and worked his way through Yale University, where he graduated with honors and was the captain of the varsity baseball team. He also graduated with honors from Harvard Law School. While at Harvard, he earned a commission in the U.S. Navy as a JAG officer. During his active-duty service, Ron deployed to Iraq as an adviser to a U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
