<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Asa Hutchinson on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Asa Hutchinson on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Asa Hutchinson biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/bio/</guid>
      <description>gov. William Asa Hutchinson bio William Asa Hutchinson first gained national attention as the youngest district attorney in the nation in 1982. He went on to represent the Third District of Arkansas in Congress as a Republican from 1997 to 2001, resigning his post on August 6, 2001, to become the director of the Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA). Hutchinson left the DEA to become the Under Secretary for Border and Transportation Security at the Department of Homeland Security, a post he held from 2003 to 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asa Hutchinson politicals</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/politics/</guid>
      <description>Asa Hutchinson is the 46th governor of the State of Arkansas. In 2018, he was re-elected with 65% of the vote, having received more votes than any other candidate for governor in the state&amp;rsquo;s history.
He has won recognition for the state as a leader in computer science education, cut taxes by $150 million, and signed a law that exempts the retirement pay of veterans from state income tax.
President Ronald Reagan appointed Governor Hutchinson as U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spouse</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/spouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/spouse/</guid>
      <description>First Lady Susan Hutchinson brings to the Governor’s Mansion a lifetime of experience advocating for and working with children.
Immediately prior to assuming the role of First Lady, the former schoolteacher spent several years on the board of the Children’s Advocacy Center of Benton County, one of 16 non-profit Children’s Advocacy Centers around the state that work with abused children. Among other initiatives, Mrs. Hutchinson hopes to see the establishment of more Children’s Advocacy Centers throughout Arkansas.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
