<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SenGov on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in SenGov on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2017 10:02:17 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mike Flood</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/nebraska/mike-flood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/nebraska/mike-flood/</guid>
      <description>Meet Mike Flood. Mike Flood has dedicated his life to advancing conservative values, growing Nebraska&amp;rsquo;s rural communities, and creating jobs.
Raised in Norfolk, Mike started working in radio in high school, a passion that continued throughout his time in college at Notre Dame and law school at the University of Nebraska. In 1999, he founded Flood Communications and grew the company from one Norfolk radio station, US92, into a statewide network of fifteen radio stations and five TV stations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amy Klobuchar biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/minnesota/amy-klobuchar/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/minnesota/amy-klobuchar/bio/</guid>
      <description>Klobuchar was born in 1960 and grew up in Plymouth, Minnesota. She earned her B.A. graduating magna cum laude from Yale University in 1982, and she received her J.D. from the University of Chicago Law School in 1985. While attending Yale, Klobuchar interned for Vice President Walter Mondale (D).
U.S. Senator Amy Klobuchar is the first woman elected to represent the State of Minnesota in the United States Senate. Throughout her public service, Senator Klobuchar has always embraced the values she learned growing up in Minnesota.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amy Klobuchar political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/minnesota/amy-klobuchar/politic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/minnesota/amy-klobuchar/politic/</guid>
      <description>Senator Amy Klobuchar Bio Amy Jean Klobuchar is an American politician and lawyer. She is currently serving as a Senior U.S. Senator from Minnesota. She was born in Plymouth, Minnesota on May 20th, 1960.
Amy went to public schools in Plymouth and she was a valedictorian at Wayzata High school. She completed her Bachelor of Arts Degree in political science magna cum laude in 1982 from Yale University. She spent her time in Yale as an intern for the Vice-president and former senator Walter Mondale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Administrative Appeals Judges</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/aaj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/aaj/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alaska</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ak/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alaska</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ak/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private First Class</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/pfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/pfc/</guid>
      <description>Private First Class is the second-lowest rank in the Marine Corps, ranking above Private and below Lance Corporal. A Private First Class in the Marines is equivalent in paygrade to a Private (PV2) in the Army, and is a full paygrade lower then an Army Private First Class because the Marine Corps only has one Private paygrade instead of the Army&amp;rsquo;s two.
The rank of Private First Class was introduced by the Marine Corps following service in WWI in 1917 to mirror the Army&amp;rsquo;s rank structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phil Murphy bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/new-jersey/phil-murphy/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/new-jersey/phil-murphy/bio/</guid>
      <description>Governor Murphy Accomplishments Since taking office, Governor Murphy has focused on building a stronger and fairer New Jersey that works for every family. Under his leadership, New Jersey has made strides in creating and expanding economic opportunity while shrinking long-standing inequities, restoring fiscal responsibility, delivering real property tax relief, growing the state’s economy, and investing in its people.
Economy &amp;amp; Jobs Governor Murphy’s primary focus is building a stronger and fairer economy that works for every New Jersey family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Denny Heck</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/denny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/denny/</guid>
      <description>About Lieutenant Governor Denny Heck Denny Heck is humbled to serve as Washington’s 17th Lieutenant Governor. First elected in 2020, Lieutenant Governor Heck brings to the office a lifetime of experience in the public, private, and non-profit sectors.
As Lieutenant Governor, he is the President of the Washington State Senate and Chair of the Senate Rules Committee. He also serves as Acting Governor whenever Governor Inslee is out of the state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Lee biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/utah/mike-lee/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/utah/mike-lee/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Mike Lee Bio Mike‌ ‌Shumway‌ ‌Lee‌ ‌is‌ ‌an‌ ‌American‌ ‌politician‌ ‌and‌ ‌Lawyer.‌ ‌
He‌ ‌is‌ ‌serving‌ ‌as‌ ‌the‌ ‌Senior‌ ‌U.S.‌ ‌Senator‌ ‌from‌ ‌Utah.‌ ‌He‌ ‌has‌ ‌been‌ ‌a‌ ‌part‌ ‌of‌ ‌the‌ ‌Senate‌ ‌since‌ ‌2011‌ ‌as‌ ‌a‌ ‌Republican.‌ ‌Sen. Lee was born in Arizona on June 4th, 1971. He went to Timpview High School. He graduated from there in 1989. He attended Brigham Young University after graduating.
He worked as president of the Brigham Young University Student Service Association (BYUSA).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>glenn youngkin bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/bio/</guid>
      <description>Gov. ‍Glenn Youngkin bio ‍Glenn Youngkin is a homegrown Virginian who grew up in Richmond and Virginia Beach. As his father changed jobs, Governor-Elect Youngkin learned that moving around didn’t equal moving up – nothing was handed to him. From his first job washing dishes and frying eggs at a diner in Virginia Beach, he embraced hard work and responsibility to help his family when his father lost his job. His determination to succeed earned him multiple high school basketball honors in Virginia and an athletic scholarship to college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike DeWine bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/ohio/mike-dewine/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/ohio/mike-dewine/bio/</guid>
      <description>know more about Governor Mike DeWine Mike DeWine’s story is a true Ohio story. Raised in Yellow Springs, Ohio, Mike DeWine and Fran Struewing met in the first grade and married while students at Miami University. They’ve been blessed with eight children and 26 grandchildren. Family is at the core of everything Mike DeWine does, and that’s why he has devoted his life to fighting for Ohio’s families. He knows when families are strong, Ohio communities are stronger, and our future is bright.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cory Booker biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/new-jersey/cory-booker/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/new-jersey/cory-booker/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Cory Booker Bio Senator Cory Anthony Booker is an American attorney, author, and politician. He has served as a junior U.S. Senator from New Jersey since 2013. He served as the 38th Mayor of Newark. He also served on the Municipal Council of Newark.
Booker was born in Washington DC on April 27, 1969. He was born to IBM executive parents. But his family relocated to New Jersey, where he attended the Northern Valley Regional High School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Padilla biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/california/alex-padilla/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/california/alex-padilla/bio/</guid>
      <description>About the Senator Alex Padilla Senator Alex Padilla is the proud son of Mexican immigrants, his father a short-order cook and his mother a housekeeper. Alex attended Los Angeles public schools and is a graduate of MIT where he studied mechanical engineering. After graduating from MIT, Alex was elected to the Los Angeles City Council where he served as the youngest Council President in Los Angeles history and provided citywide leadership at critical times, including serving as acting Mayor during the tragedy of September 11, 2001.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob Casey biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pennsylvania/bob-casey/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pennsylvania/bob-casey/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Bob Casey Biograph Senator Robert Patrick Casey is an American politician and lawyer. He has been serving as a senior U.S. Senator from Pennsylvania under the Democrats since 2007. He was the state’s Auditor General from 1997 to 2005. He was also the state’s Treasurer from 2005 to 2007 before his election to the Senate.
Senator Bob Casey was born in Scranton, Pennsylvania, on April 13, 1960. He was of Irish descent and one of the children of the former Governor of Pennsylvania, Bob Casey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Boozman biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/bio/</guid>
      <description>John Boozman biograph John Boozman is Arkansas’s senior U.S. Senator and the dean of the state’s Congressional delegation.
A fifth-generation Arkansan, John was raised in Fort Smith and graduated from Northside High School. He went on to play football for the University of Arkansas Razorbacks while completing his pre-optometry requirements. He graduated from the Southern College of Optometry in 1977 and entered private practice that same year co-founding a family business with his brother that would ultimately become a major provider of eye care to Northwest Arkansas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know more about Dan Sullivan biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/bio/</guid>
      <description>Who is senator Dan Sullivan? Senator Dan Sullivan represents Senate District 21, which includes parts of Craighead County and Jonesboro. He was elected to the Senate in November of 2020 and was sworn in on the first day of the regular session of 2021.
Senator Sullivan is a member of the Senate Committee on City, County and Local Affairs Committee and the Senate Public Health, Welfare and Labor Committee. He is also a member of the Legislative Joint Auditing Committee and the Joint Performance Review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know more about Senator Mitch McConnell</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/kentucky/mitch-mcconnell/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/kentucky/mitch-mcconnell/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Mitch McConnell Bio Senator Addison Mitchell McConnell Jr is an American politician. He has been serving as a U.S. Senator from Kentucky under the Republicans since 1985. He is also the incumbent Senate Minority Leader. He has also served as the Minority Leader from 2007 to 2015 and Majority leader from 2015 to 2021.
Senator Mitch McConnell was born in Tuscumbia, Alabama, on February 20, 1942. During his early childhood, young McConnell had polio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyrsten Sinema biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/bio/</guid>
      <description>who is senator Kyrsten Sinema Kyrsten knows firsthand the challenges everyday Arizonans face. Born in Tucson, Kyrsten went through some tough times growing up. Her family struggled to make ends meet, and for a while they were even homeless. But they got by thanks to family, church, and hard work. Kyrsten’s childhood experience showed her the power of hard work and the importance of helping others.
Education was Kyrsten’s ticket to a better life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lindsey Graham biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/south-carolina/lindsey-graham/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/south-carolina/lindsey-graham/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Lindsey Graham Bio Senator Lindsey Olin Graham is an American lawyer and politician. He has been serving as a senior U.S. Senator from South Carolina under the Republicans since 2003. He was a member of the South Carolina House of Representatives from 1993 to 1995.
He also served four terms in the U.S. House of Representatives from 1995 to 2003. He has recently served as the chair of the Senate Committee on the Judiciary from 2019 to 2021.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Kelly biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/mark-kelly/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/mark-kelly/bio/</guid>
      <description>Captain Mark Kelly is a retired U.S. Navy combat pilot, engineer, and NASA astronaut. He lives in Tucson with his wife, former Congresswoman Gabby Giffords.
Mark is the son of two police officers, and he attended public schools from elementary school through the U.S. Merchant Marine Academy and U.S. Naval Postgraduate School. As a naval aviator he made two deployments to the First Gulf War on the aircraft carrier the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike Braun</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/indiana/mike-braun/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/indiana/mike-braun/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Mike Braun Biograph Senator Michael K. Braun is an American politician and businessman. He has been serving as a junior US Senator from Indiana under the Republicans since 2018. He was a member of the Indiana House of Representatives. He represented the 63rd district from 2014 to 2017.
Braun was born in Jasper, Indiana, on March 24, 1954. He graduated from Jasper High School in 1972 and enrolled at Wabash College.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ron Johnson biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/wisconsin/ron-johnson/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/wisconsin/ron-johnson/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Ron Johnson Biograph Senator Ronald Harold Johnson (R) is an American businessman and politician. He is serving as a senior U.S. Senator from Wisconsin under the Republican party.
Johnson was born in Mankato, Minnesota, on April 8, 1955. During his childhood, he delivered newspapers. He also worked as a caddy, a baled hay, and a dishwasher.
He attended Edina High School and graduated in 1973. He enrolled at the University of Minnesota and graduated with a B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shelley Moore Capito biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/west-virginia/shelley-moore-capito/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/west-virginia/shelley-moore-capito/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Shelley Moore Capito Biograph Senator Shelley Wellons Moore Capito (R) is an American politician and educator. She has been serving as a U.S. Senator from West Virginia under the Republicans since 2015. She was a University counselor and also a former member of the U.S. House of Representatives.
Capito was born in Glen Dale, West Virginia, on November 26, 1953. She attended the Holton-Arms School. She earned her Bachelor’s degree from Duke University in 1975.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tammy Baldwin biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/wisconsin/tammy-baldwin/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/wisconsin/tammy-baldwin/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Tammy Baldwin Biograph Senator Tammy Suzanne Green Baldwin (D) is an American lawyer and politician. She has been serving as a junior U.S. Senator from Wisconsin under the Democrats since 2013. She was a member of the Wisconsin State Assembly from 1992 to 1998. She also served as a member of the U.S. House of Reps from 1999 to 2013.
Baldwin was born in Madison, Wisconsin, on February 11, 1962.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Cotton biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/tom-cotton/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/tom-cotton/bio/</guid>
      <description>Tom Cotton is a United States Senator from Arkansas. Tom’s committees include the Judiciary Committee, where he serves as the Ranking Member for the Subcommittee on Criminal Justice and Counterterrorism, the Intelligence Committee, and the Armed Services Committee, where he serves as the Ranking Member of the Air Land Power Subcommittee.
Tom grew up on his family’s cattle farm in Yell County. He graduated from Dardanelle High School, Harvard, and Harvard Law School.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tom Cotton political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/tom-cotton/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/tom-cotton/political/</guid>
      <description>who is Tom Cotton? Tom Cotton (Republican Party) is a member of the U.S. Senate from Arkansas. He assumed office on January 6, 2015. His current term ends on January 3, 2027.
Cotton (Republican Party) ran for re-election to the U.S. Senate to represent Arkansas. He won in the general election on November 3, 2020.
Cotton won election to the seat formerly held by Democrat Mark Pryor in 2014. The 2014 race between Cotton and Pryor was rated a toss-up by both Cook Political Report and Sabato&amp;rsquo;s Crystal Ball.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chuck Schumer biograph </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/new-york/chuck-schumer/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/new-york/chuck-schumer/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Chuck Schumer Biograph Senator Charles Ellis Schumer is an American politician. He is a senior U.S. Senator from New York under the Democrats since 1999. He has been the Senate Majority leader since January 2021. He is also the dean of the congressional delegation in New York.
Schumer was a member of the New York State Assembly from 1975 to 1980. He was later elected to the U.S. House of Representatives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jerry Moran biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/kansas/jerry-moran/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/kansas/jerry-moran/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Jerry Moran Biograph Senator Gerald Wesley Moran is an American lawyer and politician. He is serving as a senior U.S. Senator from Kansas under the Republicans. He was a member of the U.S. House of Representatives from Kansas 1st district.
Senator Jerry Moran was born in Great Bend, Kansas, on May 29th, 1954. Raised at Plainville, Moran graduated from the University of Kansas with a B.A. in economics in 1976.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Shelby biograph </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/bio/</guid>
      <description>biograph Born in Birmingham, Alabama, Shelby received his law degree from the Birmingham School of Law in Birmingham, Alabama, in 1961. After law school in 1963, he went on to Senator Richard Shelby is the senior United States Senator from the State of Alabama. He was first elected to the U.S. Senate in 1986 and is currently in his sixth term.
Senator Shelby is the former chairman and current vice chair of the Senate Committee on Appropriations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rob Portman biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/ohio/rob-portman/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/ohio/rob-portman/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Rob Portman Biograph Senator Rob Portman is an American politician and attorney. He has been serving as a junior U.S. Senator from Ohio under the Republican since 2010. He also served as a member of the U.S. House of Representatives from 1993 to 2005.
Senator Rob Portman was born in Cincinnati, Ohio, on December 19, 1955. He graduated from the Cincinnati Country Day School in 1974. He then enrolled at Dartmouth College, where he earned a B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tim Scott biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/south-carolina/tim-scott/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/south-carolina/tim-scott/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Tim Scott biograph Senator Timothy Eugene Scott is an American businessman and politician. He has been serving as a junior US Senator from South Carolina under the Republicans since 2013. He was a member of the US House of Representatives from 2011 to 2013. He also served as a member of the South Carolina House of Assembly from 1998 to 2008.
Senator Tim Scott was born in North Charleston, South Carolina, on September 19, 1965.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Marsha Blackburn biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/tennessee/marsha-blackburn/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/tennessee/marsha-blackburn/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Marsha Blackburn Biograph Senator Marsha Blackburn is an American politician and businesswoman. He has been serving as a senior US Senator from Tennessee under the Republicans since 2018. She was a member of the State Senate from 1999 to 2003. She was also a member of the US House of Representatives from 2003 to 2019.
Marsha was born in Laurel, Mississippi, on June 6, 1952. She was a beauty pageant winner back at high school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raphael Warnock biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/georgia/raphael-warnock/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/georgia/raphael-warnock/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Raphael Warnock Biograph Senator Raphael Gamaliel Warnock is an American politician and pastor. He is serving as a junior U.S. Senator from Georgia under the Democrats since 2021. He is a senior pastor of the Ebenezer Baptist Church in Atlanta, Georgia.
Warnock was born in Savannah, Georgia, on July 23, 1969. He was born to a war veteran dad where he grew up to learn auto mechanic works. He also learned to weld and later opened a junk car restoration business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mazie Hirono biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/hawaii/mazie-hirono/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/hawaii/mazie-hirono/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Mazie Hirono Biograph Senator Mazie Hirono is a Japanese-born American politician and lawyer. She has represented Hawaii as a junior U.S. Senator under the Democrats since 2013.
Hirono was previously a member of the Hawaii House of Representatives from 1981 to 1985. She also represented Hawaii’s 2nd District in the U.S. House of Representatives from 2007 to 2013.
Hirono was born in Koori, Fukushima city, Japan, on November 3, 1947.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patty Murray biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/washington/patty-murray/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/washington/patty-murray/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Patty Murray Biograph Senator Patricia Lynn Murray (D) is an American educator and politician. She has been serving as a senior U.S. Senator from Washington under the Democrats since 1993. She also served as a member of the Washing State Senate from 1989 to 1993.
Murray was born in Brothel, Washington, on Oct 11, 1950. She was born to an accountant mom and a war veteran dad. As a teenager, Murray and her family struggled financially.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ted Cruz biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/texas/ted-cruz/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/texas/ted-cruz/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Ted Cruz Biograph Rafael Edward Cruz is an American attorney and politician.
He is currently serving as the Junior U.S. Senator for Texas. He was born in Alberta, Canada on December 22nd, 1970. He went to two private high schools, Faith West Academy and Second Baptist High School. He graduated from there in 1988 as a valedictorian.
He went to Princeton University in 1992. He graduated cum Laude with a B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kathy Hochul bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/bio/</guid>
      <description>know more about Kathy Hochul Kathy Hochul biograph Kathy Hochul is the 57th and first female Governor of New York State. Governor Kathy Hochul began her career in public service on her local Town Board before serving as Erie County Clerk, and then as a member of Congress for New York’s 26th Congressional District. She more recently served in statewide office as Lieutenant Governor and now as the first female Governor of the State of New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roger W. Marshall biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/kansas/roger-marshall/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/kansas/roger-marshall/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Roger Marshall Bio Senator Roger Wayne Marshall (R) is an American physician and politician. He has been serving as a junior U.S. Senator from Kansas under the Republican since 2021. He was a member of the U.S. House of Representatives from 2017 to 2021.
Marshall was born in El Dorado, Kansas, on August 9, 1960. He attended Butler Community College. But, he graduated from Kansas State University with a Bachelor’s degree in Biochemistry in 1982.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Tuberville biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/bio/</guid>
      <description>who is Tommy Tuberville? EARLY LIFE Coach Tuberville was born in Camden, Arkansas on September 18, 1954, the third of three children of Olive and Charles Tuberville.
College Football&amp;rsquo;s 2004 Coach of the Year and two-time SEC Coach of the Year, Tommy Tuberville is most often recognized for his success on the field. But it is the legacy of his father, a highly decorated WWII veteran and Purple Heart recipient, that motivates Coach Tuberville to give back to the brave men and women of the United States Armed Forces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cynthia M. Lummis bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/wyoming/cynthia-lummis/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/wyoming/cynthia-lummis/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Cynthia Lummis Biograph Senator Cynthia Marie Lummis Wiederspahn (R) is an American politician. She is serving as a junior US Senator from Wyoming. She was a member of the state’s House of Representatives. She also served in the Wyoming Senate before her election to the US House of Representatives.
Lummis was born in Cheyenne, Wyoming, on September 10, 1954. Senator Cynthia Lummis attended Cheyenne East High School. She earned her Bachelor’s degree in Animal Science from the University of Wyoming in 1976.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cindy Hyde-Smith biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/cindy-hyde-smith/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mississippi/cindy-hyde-smith/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Cindy Hyde-Smith Biograph Cindy Hyde-Smith is an American politician. She is serving as a junior U.S. Senator from Mississippi. She is a member of the Republican Party. She is currently a member of the Mississippi State Senate.
Hyde-Smith was Born in Brookhaven, Mississippi. She went to Copiah–Lincoln Community College for an Associate of Arts (AA) degree. She earned the degree of Bachelor of Arts (BA) from the University of Southern Mississippi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doug Jones biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/doug-jones/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/doug-jones/bio/</guid>
      <description>senator Doug Jones biograph Gordon Douglas Jones (born May 4, 1954) is an American attorney, former prosecutor and politician serving as the junior United States Senator from Alabama since 2018. A member of the Democratic Party, he was a United States Attorney for the Northern District of Alabama from 1997 to 2001.
Jones was born in Fairfield, Alabama, and is a graduate of the University of Alabama and Cumberland School of Law at Samford University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Barrasso biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/wyoming/john-barrasso/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/wyoming/john-barrasso/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator John Barrasso Biograph Senator John Barrasso (R) is an American physician and politician. He has been serving as a senior U.S. Senator from Wyoming under the Democrats since 2008. He also served as a member of the Wyoming State Senate from 2002 to 2007.
Barrasso was born in Reading, Pennsylvania, on July 21, 1952. He graduated from Central Catholic High School in 1970. He enrolled at the Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute and studied for two years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Murkowski biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/bio/</guid>
      <description>senator Dan Sullivan biograph Lisa Murkowski, Alaska’s senior U.S. Senator, is a third generation Alaskan proudly serving as the first Alaskan born senator. Murkowski was born in Ketchikan and raised in towns across the state, including Wrangell, Juneau, Fairbanks, and Anchorage. She is married to Verne Martell and they have two grown sons. Lisa loves spending time in the Alaska outdoors. She’s an avid skier, has hiked on glaciers, enjoys fall duck hunts, and has a pretty impressive King Salmon mounted on her office wall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patrick Leahy</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/vermont/patrick-leahy/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/vermont/patrick-leahy/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Patrick Leahy Bio Patrick Joseph Leahy (D) is the senior-most and longest-serving United States senator from Vermont. He won the elections of the United States Senate as a Democrat in 1974. He is a senior politician and currently serving as the President pro tempore of the United States for the 2nd time.
He holds the record to be both the only Democrat and longest-serving senator from Vermont.
Leahy was born to Alba and Howard Francis Leahy in Montpelier, Vermont.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sherrod Brown bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/ohio/sherrod-brown/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/ohio/sherrod-brown/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Sherrod Brown Biograph Senator Sherrod Campbell Brown is an American educator and politician. He has been serving as a senior US Senator from Ohio under the Democrats since 2007. He was a member of the US House of Representatives from 1993 to 2007. He represented Ohio’s 13th District. He also served as a member of the Ohio House of Representatives.
Brown was born in Mansfield, Ohio, on November 9, 1952.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asa Hutchinson biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/bio/</guid>
      <description>gov. William Asa Hutchinson bio William Asa Hutchinson first gained national attention as the youngest district attorney in the nation in 1982. He went on to represent the Third District of Arkansas in Congress as a Republican from 1997 to 2001, resigning his post on August 6, 2001, to become the director of the Drug Enforcement Administration (DEA). Hutchinson left the DEA to become the Under Secretary for Border and Transportation Security at the Department of Homeland Security, a post he held from 2003 to 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asa Hutchinson politicals</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/politics/</guid>
      <description>Asa Hutchinson is the 46th governor of the State of Arkansas. In 2018, he was re-elected with 65% of the vote, having received more votes than any other candidate for governor in the state&amp;rsquo;s history.
He has won recognition for the state as a leader in computer science education, cut taxes by $150 million, and signed a law that exempts the retirement pay of veterans from state income tax.
President Ronald Reagan appointed Governor Hutchinson as U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bill Lee bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/tennessee/bill-lee/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/tennessee/bill-lee/bio/</guid>
      <description>know more about gov Bill Lee I’m not a politician. I’m a cattle farmer, a businessman, a father and grandfather, and a seventh generation Tennessean. At my company, I work with electricians, pipe fitters, and plumbers. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent a good part of my life doing what I can to make life better for them, and now I&amp;rsquo;d like to try to make life a little better for six and a half million Tennesseans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dan McKee biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/rhode-island/dan-mcKee/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/rhode-island/dan-mcKee/bio/</guid>
      <description>Know more about Dan McKee Daniel J. McKee was sworn in as the 76th Governor of Rhode Island on March 2, 2021. As lieutenant governor from 2015 to 2021, Dan focused on creating more economic opportunity for all Rhode Island families and building solvent communities.
As a small businessman and elected official, he has spent his adult life advocating for positive change in Rhode Island. His record is one of strong fiscal management, visionary education initiatives and thoughtful economic development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jennifer Siebel Newsom</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/california/gavin-newsom/jennifer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/california/gavin-newsom/jennifer/</guid>
      <description>First Partner Jennifer Siebel Newsom Jennifer Siebel Newsom is the First Partner of California, award-winning filmmaker, advocate, and mother of four.
Jennifer Siebel Newsom is the First Partner of California, an award-winning filmmaker, and an influential advocate and thought leader on gender equality. As First Partner, Jennifer is a voice and partner to working moms and families throughout the state — committed to creating a California for ALL Women and California for ALL Kids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Carney bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/delaware/john-carney/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/delaware/john-carney/bio/</guid>
      <description>know more about John Charles Carney Jr John Charles Carney Jr. (born May 20, 1956) is an American politician who is the 74th and current Governor of Delaware since January 2017. He is a member of the Democratic Party, and served as the U.S. Representative for Delaware&amp;rsquo;s at-large congressional district from 2011 to 2017 prior to his governorship. Carney was also the 24th Lieutenant Governor of Delaware from 2001 to 2009 and served as Delaware&amp;rsquo;s Secretary of Finance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Larry Hogan bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/bio/</guid>
      <description>About Governor Lawrence J. Hogan Governor Lawrence J. Hogan, Jr. was sworn in as the 62nd governor of the State of Maryland on January 21, 2015. In 2018, he was overwhelmingly re-elected to a second four-year term, receiving the most votes of any Maryland gubernatorial candidate and becoming only the second Republican governor to be re-elected in the 242-year history of the state.
In his first inaugural address, Governor Hogan reminded citizens of Maryland’s history as a state of middle temperament and pledged to advance the best ideas, regardless of which side of the political aisle they come from.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muriel Bowser bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/washingtondc/muriel-bowser/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/washingtondc/muriel-bowser/bio/</guid>
      <description>know more about Gov Muriel Bowser Muriel Bowser is committed to making sure every Washingtonian gets a fair shot in a growing and prosperous Washington, DC. Her administration is focused on making DC’s prosperity more inclusive, advancing DC values, and building safer, stronger, and healthier neighborhoods across DC’s eight wards.
Washington, DC is unique in the American political system – the mayor, DC’s chief executive, functions as a governor, county executive, and mayor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roger Wicker biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/bio/</guid>
      <description>who is Roger F. Wicker ? Roger F. Wicker has represented Mississippi in the United States Senate since December 2007. During his time in the Senate, Wicker has championed pro-growth policies to create jobs, limit federal overreach, protect life, and maintain a strong national defense.
Wicker is the ranking member of the Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation for the 117th Congress. He served as chairman of the full committee during the 116th Congress after previously serving as the chairman of the Senate Commerce Subcommittee on Communications, Technology, Innovation, and the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spencer Cox bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/utah/spencer-cox/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/utah/spencer-cox/bio/</guid>
      <description>Know more about Governor Spencer Cox A sixth-generation Utahn, Gov. Spencer J. Cox was born and raised in Fairview, a town of 1,247 residents located about two hours south of Salt Lake City. He graduated from Snow College, Utah State University and Washington and Lee University School of Law.
Cox met Abby Palmer at age 16 and they have been smitten with each other ever since. After Spencer’s service as a missionary in Mexico, the couple married and moved away to continue their education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tate Reeves bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/bio/</guid>
      <description>know more About Governor Tate Reeves As the 65th Governor of Mississippi, Tate Reeves continues to build on his strong record as a conservative leader who fights to guard taxpayers’ dollars, improve educational opportunity, and grow new careers so that our state’s best and brightest can raise their families and thrive here at home.
In his inaugural address, Governor Reeves promised that this would be an administration for all Mississippi. He committed to a mission to create a climate where good careers are plentiful with every Mississippian prepared to pursue them, as he has every single day of his time serving our state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thom Tillis </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/north-carolina/thom-tillis/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/north-carolina/thom-tillis/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Thom Tillis Bio Senator Thomas Rolland Tillis is an American politician. He has served as a junior U.S. Senator from North Carolina as a Republican since 2015. He was also a member of the North Carolina House of Reps.
Senator Thom Tillis was born on August 30, 1960, in Jacksonville, Florida. He was born to Margue and Thomas Raymond Tillis, a boat draftsman. In 1978, Tillis graduated from high school, after which he left home to get a job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tina Smith bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/bio/</guid>
      <description>I have been honored to serve as your Senator since January 2018 and I’m proud of the work we’ve done together since then. I moved to Minnesota the summer of 1984 with my new husband Archie. My first job in Minnesota was at General Mills. Archie and I moved to St. Louis Park, had our two sons Sam and Mason (who are now married!), and found our life in Minnesota. A few years later I started my own business, and at the same time got more active in my community volunteering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yumi Hogan</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/maryland/larry-hogan/bio/</guid>
      <description>Maryland’s First Lady Yumi Hogan Maryland’s First Lady, Yumi Hogan, is the first Korean American First Lady in the United States and the first Asian American First Lady of Maryland. She is the youngest of eight children and grew up on a farm in the countryside of South Korea. Mrs. Hogan is a first-generation Korean American, the mother of three daughters, and has four grandchildren.
Mrs. Hogan is an accomplished artist and adjunct professor at Maryland Institute College of Art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deb Fischer bio </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/nebraska/deb-fischer/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/nebraska/deb-fischer/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Deb Fischer Bio Senator Debra Strobel Fischer is an American politician. She has been serving as the senior U.S. Senator from Nebraska under the Republican since 2013. She was a member of the rural high school board of Education from 1990 to 2004. She also served two terms as a representative in the Nebraska Legislature.
Fischer was born on March 1, 1951, in Lincoln, Nebraska. She studied at Lincoln Southeast High school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/vermont/bernie-sanders/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 11:48:55 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/vermont/bernie-sanders/bio/</guid>
      <description>Senator Bernie Sanders Biograph Bernie Sanders (I) is an Independent US Senator, American activist, and political scientist.
Senator Bernie Sanders has served as a junior United States senator from Vermont. Bernard Sanders was born in the Brooklyn borough of New York City on 8 September 1941. His parents were Jews who belonged to a working-class family.
Sanders was into politics from his early childhood. He got his early education from P.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pedro Pierluisi bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/puerto-rico/pedro-pierluisi/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/puerto-rico/pedro-pierluisi/bio/</guid>
      <description>Know more about Gov.Pedro Pierluisi Pedro Pierluisi is the Governor of Puerto Rico and presides over the New Progressive Party. He was elected on November 3, 2020. Pierluisi is a lawyer from San Juan with 35 years of experience in the public and private sectors.
He began his professional career in Washington, D.C. as an assistant to Resident Commissioner Baltasar Corrada del Rio. He then practiced for six years as a trial lawyer in that city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Administrative Law Judges</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/alj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/alj/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alabama</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/al/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/al/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alabama</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/al/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/al/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American samoa</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/as/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/as/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>American samoa</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/as/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/as/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arizona</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/az/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/az/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arizona</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/az/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/az/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arkansas</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ar/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>california</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ca/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>california</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ca/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/co/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/co/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colorado</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/co/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/co/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ct/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecticut</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ct/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ct/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delaware</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/de/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/de/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delaware</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/de/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/de/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>District of Columbia</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/dc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>District of Columbia</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/dc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Florida</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/fl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/fl/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Florida</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/fl/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/fl/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Georgia</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ga/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ga/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Georgia</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ga/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ga/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guam </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/gu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/gu/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guam </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/gu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/gu/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/hi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/hi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hawaii</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/hi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/hi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idaho</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/id/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/id/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Idaho</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/id/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/id/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illinois</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/il/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/il/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illinois</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/il/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/il/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indiana</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/in/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Indiana</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/in/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iowa</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iowa</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ia/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kansas</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ky/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kentucky</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ky/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/la/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Louisiana</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/la/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/la/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maine</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/me/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maine</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/me/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/me/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maryland </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/md/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/md/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maryland </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/md/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/md/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massachusetts</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ma/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Massachusetts</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ma/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ma/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michigan</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mn/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minnesota</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mn/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ms/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mississippi </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ms/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missouri</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Missouri</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montana</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Montana</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ne/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ne/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nebraska</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ne/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ne/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nevada</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nh/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Hampshire</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nh/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nj/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Jersey</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nj/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Mexico</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nm/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ny/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ny/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>North Carolina</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>North Carolina</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>North Dakota</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/nd/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>North Dakota</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/nd/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Mariana Islands</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/mp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Northern Mariana Islands</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/mp/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ohio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/oh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/oh/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ohio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/oh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/oh/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ok/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ok/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oklahoma</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ok/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ok/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oregon</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/or/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/or/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oregon</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/or/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/or/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/pa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/pa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pennsylvania</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/pa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/pa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/pr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Puerto Rico</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/pr/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhode Island</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ri/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rhode Island</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ri/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ri/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Carolina</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/sc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Carolina</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/sc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/sc/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Dakota</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/sd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/sd/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>South Dakota</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/sd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/sd/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/tn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/tn/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tennessee</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/tn/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/tn/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/tx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/tx/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Texas</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/tx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/tx/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utah</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/ut/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utah</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/ut/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vermont</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/vt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/vt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vermont</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/vt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/vt/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Islands</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/vi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/vi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgin Islands</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/vi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/vi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virginia</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/va/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/va/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virginia</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/va/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/va/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/wa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/wa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Washington</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/wa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/wa/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/wv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/wv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Virginia</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/wv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/wv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/wi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/wi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wisconsin</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/wi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/wi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/wy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/gs/wy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wyoming </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/wy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/leo/wy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lance Corporal</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/lcpl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/lcpl/</guid>
      <description>Lance Corporal is the third enlisted rank in the Marine Corps, equivalent to a Private First Class in the Army. Unlike the rank of Corporal, a Lance Corporal is not considered a non-commissioned officer. However, Marines promoted to this rank are expected to show a degree of leadership and skill in serving as role models for newly enlisted recruits.
While the Army temporarily had Lance Corporals in the 1960s, the Marine Corps is currently the only branch of the armed forces that maintains this rank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letitia James</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/james/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/james/</guid>
      <description>About the Attorney General Letitia James Letitia “Tish” James is the 67th Attorney General for the State of New York. With decades of work, she is an experienced attorney and public servant with a long record of accomplishments. She is the first woman of color to hold statewide office in New York and the first woman to be elected Attorney General.
In 2013, Ms. James was elected Public Advocate for the City of New York and became the first woman of color to hold citywide office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Winsome Sears</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/winsome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/winsome/</guid>
      <description>About Lieutenant Governor Winsome Earle-Sears Winsome Earle-Sears, a native of Kingston, Jamaica, immigrated to the United States at the age of six. She is proud to have served in the United States Marine Corps. In addition to her various appointments, she has served as the Vice President of the Virginia State Board of Education; and as a presidential appointee to the US Census Bureau, as co-chair of the African American Committee; and the Advisory Committee on Women Veterans to the Secretary of Veterans Affairs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/bob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/bob/</guid>
      <description>About Washington State Attorney General Bob Ferguson Bob Ferguson is Washington State’s 18th Attorney General. As the state’s chief legal officer, Bob is committed to protecting the people of Washington against powerful interests that don’t play by the rules. He is a fourth-generation Washingtonian, a graduate of the University of Washington and New York University law school. Bob and his wife, Colleen, are the proud parents of 14-year-old twins, Jack and Katie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spouse</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/ohio/mike-dewine/spouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/ohio/mike-dewine/spouse/</guid>
      <description>know more about First Lady Fran DeWine Mike DeWine and Fran Struewing met in the first grade and married while students at Miami University. They are the parents of 8 wonderful and diverse children, though daughter Becky was tragically lost in an auto accident in 1993. They now have 26 wonderful grandchildren. Fran loves to cook for her family and there is nothing she enjoys more than large family gatherings with aunts and uncles, cousins and grandparents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dan Sullivan Political Views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/political/</guid>
      <description>Political Views Abortion / LGBT Sullivan opposes abortion, except in cases of rape, incest, or threat to the life of the mother; he also has voiced his opposition to same-sex marriage.
Healthcare He opposes the Affordable Care Act and believes it should be repealed and replaced.
Undocumented Immigrants &amp;amp; Energy Sullivan is against granting amnesty for undocumented immigrants, and is a proponent of an &amp;ldquo;all-of-the-above&amp;rdquo; energy policy, including increased drilling for oil.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alex Padilla political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/california/alex-padilla/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/california/alex-padilla/political/</guid>
      <description>who is senator Alex Padilla ? Alex Padilla (Democratic Party) is a member of the U.S. Senate from California. He assumed office on January 20, 2021. His current term ends on January 3, 2023.
Padilla (Democratic Party) is running for re-election to the U.S. Senate to represent California. He declared candidacy for the primary scheduled on June 7, 2022.
On December 22, 2020, California Gov. Gavin Newsom (D) appointed Padilla to fill the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>John Boozman political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/john-boozman/political/</guid>
      <description>John&amp;rsquo;s political view Issues John Boozman, a successful businessman and life-long resident of Arkansas, has represented Arkansas in the United States Senate for six years, establishing a record as a strong supporter of the values and principles that Arkansans hold dearly. He will continue this same commitment to the people of the Natural State in his second term as your United States Senator.
Winning the War on Terror Requires Confronting Radical Islam If anyone embodies a twisted view of radical Islam, it is the Islamic State (ISIS) terror organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyrsten Sinema Political Views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/political/</guid>
      <description>Political Views Sinema has been described as a centrist or moderate Democrat. According to National Journal&amp;rsquo;s 2013 Vote Ratings, her votes place her near the center of their liberal-conservative scale. The National Journal gave her a composite ideology score of 57% liberal and 43% conservative. According to the Bipartisan Index created by The Lugar Center and the McCourt School of Public Policy, Sinema was the sixth most bipartisan member of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mark Kelly Political Views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/mark-kelly/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/mark-kelly/political/</guid>
      <description>Health Care As a cancer survivor and the husband of Gabby Giffords, who was nearly killed in a shooting and owes her life to quality medical care, Mark has a deep appreciation for the importance of health care and coverage that you can rely on. Mark knows that he and Gabby were fortunate to have good insurance that covered the lifesaving care they needed, but that many Arizona families lack affordable health coverage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Shelby political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/political-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/political-views/</guid>
      <description>political Views Gun law Shelby has an A+ rating from the National Rifle Association for his support of gun rights. In 2016, Shelby voted against the Feinstein Amendment, which sought to stop the sale of firearms to people known or suspected to be terrorists. Upon being asked by Scott Wapner on why he voted against it, Shelby said &amp;ldquo;I do believe that we should keep guns out of the hands of terrorists, would-be terrorists, and a lot of other people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Tuberville political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/political-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/political-view/</guid>
      <description>SERVING THOSE WHO SERVED Changing The Way We Treat Our Veterans My father was a highly decorated WWII veteran and Purple Heart recipient, and that is why I am so passionate about changing the way our nation treats its Veterans. President Trump is off to a good start – Veteran unemployment is at its lowest point in history: 2.3%. But we can and must do more to help our Veterans re-enter the workforce and society.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doug Jones Political Views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/doug-jones/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/doug-jones/political/</guid>
      <description>Political Views Overall The editorial board of The Birmingham News has described Jones as a &amp;ldquo;moderate Democrat&amp;rdquo;. Former Alabama Democratic Party chair Giles Perkins described Jones as &amp;ldquo;a moderate, middle-of-the-road guy&amp;rdquo;. Describing his own views, Jones said: &amp;ldquo;If you look at the positions I&amp;rsquo;ve got on health care, if you look at the positions I got on jobsâ€”you should look at the support I have from the business communityâ€”I think I&amp;rsquo;m pretty mainstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Murkowski Political Views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/political/</guid>
      <description>Political Views Senator Lisa Murkowski is a moderate Republican. Since winning re-election in 2010, her voting record has been deemed by some as &amp;ldquo;more moderate&amp;rdquo; when compared to her previous years in the Senate. The National Journal, in 2013, gave Murkowski a composite score of 56% conservative and 45% liberal. The National Journal ranked her as the 56th most liberal and 44th most conservative member of the Senate. CrowdPac, which rates politicians based on donations they receive and give, has given Murkowski a score of 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roger Wicker political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/politic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/politic/</guid>
      <description>Senator Roger Wicker Bio Roger Frederick Wicker is a senior American attorney and politician. He was born on July 5, 1951, in Pontotoc, Mississippi. He is currently serving as the senior U.S Senator from Mississippi for the last fifteen years.
A member of the Republican Party, Wicker previously served as a member of the United States House of Representatives and the Mississippi State Senate. He has worked as an officer in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spouse</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/spouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/spouse/</guid>
      <description>know more About First Lady of Mississippi Elee Williams Reeves First Lady of Mississippi, Elee Williams Reeves, grew up in Tylertown where her parents emphasized the importance of education and giving back to the community.
After graduating from McComb High School, she pursued her degree at Millsaps College in Jackson, graduating with honors. Elee also holds a Master’s degree in Business Administration from Millsaps College.
Beginning her career in 2001, Elee helps others reach their financial goals as an investment advisor with Coker &amp;amp; Palmer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tina Smith political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/politics/</guid>
      <description>Senator Tina Smith Bio Christine Elizabeth Smith is a former businesswoman and an American politician. She is currently serving in Minnesota as a Junior U.S. Senator since 2018. She is currently a member of the DFL Minnesota.
Senator Tina Smith was born on March 4th, 1958 in New Mexico. She was raised in Santa Fe. She attended Manderfield and Acequia Elementary. She completed her high school in Northern California.
After high school, she went to Stanford and completed her Bachelor’s degree in Political Science from there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boards of Contract Appeals</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/bca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/bca/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporal</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/cpl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/cpl/</guid>
      <description>A Corporal in the Marine Corps is a junior noncommissioned officer, and is equivalent in rank to the Army&amp;rsquo;s junior NCO ranks of Corporal and Specialist. Corporals usually command small contingents of Marines in combat and operations, including four-man fireteams (which may also be lead by a Lance Corporal) or eight-man squads comprising of two fireteams.
The Marine Corps specializes in small-unit operations, and as a result Corporals hold a significant amount of authority and resposibility in contrast to the lighter duties of Lance Corporals and Privates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kay James </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/james/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/james/</guid>
      <description>About Kay Coles James The Honorable Kay Coles James was born in Portsmouth, Virginia, and raised in her early years in Richmond’s housing projects to a single mother in the segregated South. Secretary James was one of the first children to take part in a historic experiment to desegregate Virginia’s all-white schools and later graduated from Hampton University.
She most recently served as the President of the Heritage Foundation, a prominent think tank in Washington, D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Rodriguez </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/robert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/robert/</guid>
      <description>About the Secretary of State Robert Rodriguez Robert J. Rodriguez is currently serving as the Secretary of State. He was nominated by Governor Kathy Hochul to serve as New York’s 68th Secretary of State.
Mr. Rodriguez is a uniquely accomplished leader and former legislator, with civic and legislative successes that have been focused strategically on investing in and developing public-good infrastructure projects, creating good-paying jobs and addressing financial disparities for historically underrepresented minorities and low-income communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Hobbs</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/hobbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/hobbs/</guid>
      <description>About Secretary of State Steve Hobbs Steve Hobbs is Washington’s 16th Secretary of State. He was appointed by Gov. Jay Inslee to replace Kim Wyman, who resigned mid-term to join the Department of Homeland Security’s Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA). Secretary Hobbs began his tenure Nov. 22, 2021.
As head of one of the most diverse offices in state government, Secretary Hobbs is responsible for managing state and local elections, corporation and charity filings, Washington State Library, Washington Talking Book &amp;amp; Braille Library, and Washington State Archives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyrsten Sinema campaign manifest</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/campaign/</guid>
      <description>FIXING A DYSFUNCTIONAL WASHINGTON Arizonans know Washington is dysfunctional. Too many politicians are more concerned about the next election than doing what’s best for everyday people. Many think the rules we all follow don’t apply to them.
Not Kyrsten.
Kyrsten was ranked the third most independent member of Congress. Kyrsten supports the No Budget, No Pay bill that says if Congress doesn’t pass a budget, they shouldn’t get paid. She voted against her own pay raise and cosponsored legislation to dock pay for members of Congress who engage in bad behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spouse</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/spouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arkansas/asa-hutchinson/spouse/</guid>
      <description>First Lady Susan Hutchinson brings to the Governor’s Mansion a lifetime of experience advocating for and working with children.
Immediately prior to assuming the role of First Lady, the former schoolteacher spent several years on the board of the Children’s Advocacy Center of Benton County, one of 16 non-profit Children’s Advocacy Centers around the state that work with abused children. Among other initiatives, Mrs. Hutchinson hopes to see the establishment of more Children’s Advocacy Centers throughout Arkansas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Executive Schedule Rates</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/es/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/es/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgt/</guid>
      <description>Sergeant is a junior noncommissioned officer rank in the USMC, and the oldest rank in the Marine Corps. Sergeants serve as squad leaders in combat operations, and lead a squad of eight soldiers including one or more Corporals.
Because the Marine Corps operates many missions on the fireteam and squad level, Marine Corps sergeants often have a great deal of leadership and responsibility in carrying out their objectives.
Because of their expanded role in direct combat oparations, promotion to sergeant is handled on a case-by-case basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jason Miyares</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/jason/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/virginia/glenn-youngkin/jason/</guid>
      <description>About the Attorney General Jason Miyares Attorney General Jason Miyares&amp;rsquo; story doesn&amp;rsquo;t start in Virginia Beach, Virginia, but in Havana, Cuba when his mother, Miriam Miyares, fled communist Cuba, penniless and homeless. She taught Jason a love for freedom, democracy, and that America is indeed the “last best hope on earth.” A product of Virginia public schools, Jason graduated with a Bachelor’s in Business Administration from James Madison University and received his J.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senior-Level and Professional Positions</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/slst/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/slst/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/ssgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/ssgt/</guid>
      <description>Staff Sergeant is the first of the staff non-commissioned officer ranks in the United States Marine Corps. Generally experienced Marines with 10 to 13 years of service, Staff Sergeants most often serve as a platoon sergeant for a platoon consisting of 30 or more Marines.
As a platoon sergeant, Staff Sergeants may act as the top tactical advisor to their platoon commander during combat and support operations. In day-to-day deployment and training, a staff sergeant will also assist with training and administrative operation of his platoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locality Rates for  Members of Boards of Contract Appeals</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/lbca/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/lbca/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gunnery Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/gysgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/gysgt/</guid>
      <description>A Gunnery Sergeant in the United States Marine Corps is a specialized non-commissioned officer who manages firepower and logistics for a company-sized unit of Marines.
The rank of Gunnery Sergeant is unique to the Marine Corps, and was introduced in the 19th century. While serving aboard Navy vessels, Marine contingents were expected to help man the ship&amp;rsquo;s weapons in gun crews of four to five marines. The leader of each gun crew was a specialized Marine who trained his gun crew in firing procedure, ammunition handling, and other essential skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Members of the Senior Executive Service</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/se/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/se/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/msgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/msgt/</guid>
      <description>First Sergeant is a senior non-commissioned officer&amp;rsquo;s rank in the United States Marine Corps. A First Sergeant shares the E-8 paygrade with Master Sergeant, although the two ranks have separate spheres of responsibility.
A First Sergeant serves as the senior enlisted advisor to the commander of a medium-to-large unit of Marines, such as a platoon or a company. As the senior enlisted advisor, First Sergeants hold the responsiobility of being the main bridge between enlisted Marines and their company commander.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locality Rates for Administrative Law Judges</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/lalj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/lalj/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/1stsgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/1stsgt/</guid>
      <description>First Sergeant is a senior non-commissioned officer&amp;rsquo;s rank in the United States Marine Corps. A First Sergeant shares the E-8 paygrade with Master Sergeant, although the two ranks have separate spheres of responsibility.
A First Sergeant serves as the senior enlisted advisor to the commander of a medium-to-large unit of Marines, such as a platoon or a company. As the senior enlisted advisor, First Sergeants hold the responsiobility of being the main bridge between enlisted Marines and their company commander.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locality Rates for  Administrative Appeals Judges</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/laaj/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Oct 2023 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/pay/executive/laaj/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Gunnery Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/mgysgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/mgysgt/</guid>
      <description>Sergeant Major is the highest enlisted rank in the Marine Corps, and is equivalent in paygrade (but not in responsibility) to Master Gunnery Sergeant.
A Sergeant Major serves as the billeted senior enlisted advisor for the Marine Corps&amp;rsquo; largest units, including battalions and squadrons. As the senior enlisted member of their unit, Sergeant Majors serve as a bridge between the enlisted Marines and their commanders and assist in unit logistics, drilling, and disciplinary actions among their Marines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sergeant Major</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgtmaj/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgtmaj/</guid>
      <description>Sergeant Major is the highest enlisted rank in the Marine Corps, and is equivalent in paygrade (but not in responsibility) to Master Gunnery Sergeant.
A Sergeant Major serves as the billeted senior enlisted advisor for the Marine Corps&amp;rsquo; largest units, including battalions and squadrons. As the senior enlisted member of their unit, Sergeant Majors serve as a bridge between the enlisted Marines and their commanders and assist in unit logistics, drilling, and disciplinary actions among their Marines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sergeant Major Of The Marine Corps</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgtmajmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgtmajmc/</guid>
      <description>Sergeant Major is the highest enlisted rank in the Marine Corps, and is equivalent in paygrade (but not in responsibility) to Master Gunnery Sergeant.
A Sergeant Major serves as the billeted senior enlisted advisor for the Marine Corps&amp;rsquo; largest units, including battalions and squadrons. As the senior enlisted member of their unit, Sergeant Majors serve as a bridge between the enlisted Marines and their commanders and assist in unit logistics, drilling, and disciplinary actions among their Marines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Corey Stapleton  for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/corey-stapleton2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/corey-stapleton2024/</guid>
      <description>I am running for the office of President of the United States, and I firmly believe that bold action is what&amp;rsquo;s required to address the challenges we face today. We don&amp;rsquo;t have much time before the same old political operatives start influencing the choices for the 2024 elections, which are nearly two years away.
These are historically challenging times. In recent years, government spending has surged, leading to the worst inflation since the days of President Jimmy Carter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Marianne Williamson  for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/marianne-williamson2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/marianne-williamson2024/</guid>
      <description>Marianne Williamson is a renowned bestselling author, dedicated political activist, and influential spiritual thought leader.
For more than three decades, she has played a pivotal role in progressive spiritual and religious circles. She boasts an impressive literary portfolio, with 15 published books, four of which have achieved the esteemed status of #1 New York Times bestsellers.
In 1989, Williamson established Project Angel Food, a non-profit organization with a remarkable track record of delivering over 16 million meals to homebound patients battling serious illnesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Doug Burgum  for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/doug-burgum2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/doug-burgum2024/</guid>
      <description>Small Town Upbringing Doug was raised in a tiny town in North Dakota. As a freshman in high school, his life changed forever. Doug was pulled off the team bus and told his dad was dying. The community rallied around the family, and his mother went back to work. Doug learned the importance of grit and determination from his parents and still cherishes the small-town values that shaped his childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Larry Elder  for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/larry-elder2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/larry-elder2024/</guid>
      <description>America is in decline, but this decline is not inevitable. It is a choice made by detached and cynical politicians. As a California resident, I’ve seen firsthand how decades of Democrat rule have turned the Golden State, for many, into an unaffordable dystopia. I won’t let them do the same to America. We can enter a new American Golden Age, but we must choose a leader who can bring us there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mayor Francis Suarez  for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/francis-suarez2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/francis-suarez2024/</guid>
      <description>Francis X. Suarez, the 43rd Mayor of Miami and a true Miami native, is dedicated to shaping a Miami that endures for generations to come and is open to all. Mayor Suarez first came into office with an impressive mandate of 86 percent support and was subsequently re-elected with nearly 79 percent backing from the community. Throughout his tenure, he has been a strong advocate for integrating climate adaptive policies, Web 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cornel West  for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/cornel-west2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/cornel-west2024/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Cornel West, affectionately known to many as Brother West, is the Dietrich Bonhoeffer Professor of Philosophy and Christian Practice at Union Theological Seminary. Dr. West teaches on the works of Dietrich Bonhoeffer, as well as courses in Philosophy of Religion, African American Critical Thought, and a wide range of subjects - including but by no means limited to - the classics, philosophy, politics, cultural theory, literature, and music. He has a passion to communicate to a vast variety of public in order to keep alive the legacy of Martin Luther King, Jr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Chris Christie for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/chris-christie-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/chris-christie-2024/</guid>
      <description>Chris Christie: A Leader with a Record of Action In the ever-evolving landscape of American politics, one name has consistently stood out for its bold leadership and unwavering commitment to the people: Chris Christie. With a career marked by notable achievements and a firm dedication to the principles of fairness and accountability, Christie is a proven leader ready to bring his vision to the highest office in the land.
Early Life and Education Christopher James Christie, known to many simply as Chris, was born on September 6, 1962, in Newark, New Jersey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ryan Binkley for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/ryan-binkley-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/ryan-binkley-2024/</guid>
      <description>About Ryan Binkley Ryan Binkley is the President and CEO of Generational Group located in Richardson, Texas. With over 300 employees, Generational focuses on business consultancy, M&amp;amp;A, and wealth advisory for business owners throughout North America.
Ryan and his wife, Ellie, are also founders of Create Church, a multiethnic, multigenerational church in Richardson, Texas. As lead pastor, his deep passion is to see church members of all walks of life discover and live out their purpose.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Robert F. Kennedy Jr for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/robert-f-kennedy-jr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/robert-f-kennedy-jr/</guid>
      <description>Bobby Kennedy, Jr. is a lifelong Democrat known for his unwavering dedication to public service and his tireless advocacy for environmental causes. Born into a prominent political family as the son of Senator Robert F. Kennedy and the nephew of President John F. Kennedy, Bobby embarked on a career of public service early in his life.
After passing the New York State Bar, Bobby began his journey in public service, eventually emerging as one of the United States&amp;rsquo; most influential environmentalists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tim Scott for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/timescot2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/timescot2024/</guid>
      <description>Living Proof: Tim Scott&amp;rsquo;s Journey from Poverty to Politics I am living proof that America is the land of opportunity. My journey from being raised in poverty by a single mother to becoming a candidate for the presidency of the United States demonstrates the power of faith, perseverance, and patriotism. In this blog post, I will share my story and address how the Biden liberals are attacking every rung of the ladder that helped me climb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mike Pence for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/mikepence2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/mikepence2024/</guid>
      <description>Michael R. Pence was born in Columbus, Indiana, on June 7, 1959, one of six children born to Edward and Nancy Pence. As a young boy he had a front row seat to the American Dream. After his grandfather immigrated to the United States when he was 17, his family settled in the Midwest. The future Vice President watched his Mom and Dad build everything that matters—a family, a business, and a good name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative David A. Alvarez</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/david-alvarez/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/david-alvarez/</guid>
      <description>Assemblymember David Alvarez was elected to the California State Assembly in June of 2022 to represent the 80th Assembly District in San Diego County.
Assemblymember Alvarez is a small business owner and has served for fifteen years in government, including eight years as a San Diego City Councilmember. A proud advocate of the underserved in San Diego, his previous successes included building parks, libraries and fire stations in neighborhoods that did not have them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Rebecca Bauer-Kahan</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/rebecca-bauer-kahan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/rebecca-bauer-kahan/</guid>
      <description>Assemblymember Rebecca Bauer-Kahan was first elected to represent Assembly District 16 in the California State Assembly in 2018, which includes Alamo, Danville, Dublin, Lafayette, Livermore, Moraga, Orinda, Pleasanton, San Ramon, and Walnut Creek.
Rebecca is an accomplished attorney, environmental advocate, community volunteer, law professor, and mother. A Bay Area native, she is the granddaughter of refugees who came to the United States to escape the Holocaust. Their experiences inspired her to use her career and personal time to help others in her community, solve complex problems, protect civil rights, and fight to ensure everyone has the opportunity to succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Steve Bennett</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/steve-bennett/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/steve-bennett/</guid>
      <description>Assemblymember Steve Bennett was elected to the Assembly in November 2020 and represents the 38th district that includes the western part of Ventura County.
Born and raised in the Midwest, Steve developed a strong sense of community responsibility. After graduating from Brown University with an Honors Degree in Economics, Steve served his community as a high school Economics and American History teacher for over 20 years. At the same time, he advanced solutions to community problems of urban sprawl, money corrupting politics, and problems encountered by disadvantaged communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Jasmeet Bains</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/jasmeet-bains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/jasmeet-bains/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Jasmeet Bains Sworn in as Assemblymember for District 35
Assemblymember Dr. Jasmeet Bains was elected to the California State Assembly in November of 2022 to represent the 35th Assembly District.
Assemblymember Bains worked as a family doctor providing primary healthcare to families throughout the Valley. Dr. Bains also serves as a volunteer with Global Family, an organization dedicated to combating human trafficking and child abuse, on the San Joaquin Valley Air District’s Environmental Justice Advisory group, working to improve our Valley’s air and water quality and on the Taft College Foundation, fighting to expand access to higher education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Joaquin Arambula</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/joaquin-arambula/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/joaquin-arambula/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Joaquin Arambula was elected in 2016 to represent the 31st Assembly District in Fresno County in the Central Valley. He is the first Latino physician elected to the California State Assembly.
He proudly represents a district that includes a majority of the City of Fresno, the rural cities of Fowler, Sanger, Selma, Orange Cove, and Parlier and unincorporated communities in southern and eastern portions of Fresno County.
Arambula’s experience as an emergency room doctor in Selma forged his determination to improve health care for all people, especially the most vulnerable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ron DeSantis for President of the United States</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 May 2023 10:05:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-president/</guid>
      <description>Meet Ron DeSantis Ron DeSantis, a native Floridian with blue-collar roots, grew up in Dunedin under the care of his nurse mother and cable box installer father. He attended Dunedin High School before earning his way through Yale University, where he served as captain of the varsity baseball team. Ron&amp;rsquo;s dedication to education continued as he graduated with honors from Harvard Law School and earned a commission as a JAG officer in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Asa Hutchinson for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/asa2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/asa2024/</guid>
      <description>Asa Hutchinson, who served as the 46th governor of Arkansas from 2015 to 2023, made an informal announcement on April 2, 2023, about his campaign for the presidency of the United States during an exclusive interview with ABC News&amp;rsquo; Jonathan Karl. The campaign was officially launched on April 26.
In March 2023, Hutchinson expressed his belief that having &amp;ldquo;more voices right now in opposition or providing an alternative to Donald Trump is the best thing in the right direction&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Cecilia M. Aguiar-Curry</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/aguiar-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/aguiar-curry/</guid>
      <description>In November 2016, Cecilia Aguiar-Curry was elected to the California Assembly to represent the 4th District that includes all or parts of Napa, Lake, Yolo, Sonoma, Colusa and Solano counties.
Cecilia grew up in western Yolo County and has long served her community. After going to school and working in the Bay Area for several years, she moved back to her hometown of Winters where she almost immediately became active in the local community and a regional leader on several issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Dawn Addis</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/dawn-addis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/dawn-addis/</guid>
      <description>Dawn Addis was elected to the California State Assembly in 2022 to represent the 30th Assembly District. Dawn is a special education teacher who began teaching in public schools over 20 years ago, and holds a Master of Arts (MA) degree in special education from San Francisco State University.
She has teaching credentials in elementary education, secondary education and special education and is fluent in Spanish. Dawn&amp;rsquo;s long record of community involvement includes co-founding the Women&amp;rsquo;s March in San Luis Obispo and being a Planned Parenthood Central Coast Action Fund board member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Juan  Alanis</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/juanalanis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/juanalanis/</guid>
      <description>Juan Alanis began a career in public service on his 21st birthday when he proudly pinned on a badge as a law enforcement officer. For nearly three decades, he has dedicated his life to protecting others. Juan has received three awards for saving the lives of others, including a decoration for rescuing a child whose father was trying to burn down a house with his daughter inside it.
The newly created 22nd Assembly District is more than just borders on a map; for Juan, it is home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Donald Trump for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/trump-for-president-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/trump-for-president-2024/</guid>
      <description>Donald John Trump, the 45th President of the United States, has been a controversial figure both during and after his time in office. As he continues to be a prominent voice in American politics, it&amp;rsquo;s worth revisiting the policies he put forth during his presidential campaign.
Our Mission to Make America Great Again I left behind my former life because I could not sit by and watch career politicians continue bleeding this country dry and allow other nations to take advantage of us on trade, borders, foreign policy, and national defense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Governor DeSantis Unveils Legislation to Address Illegal Immigration Threats in Florida</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/gov-ron-desantis-new-legislative-proposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 10:05:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/gov-ron-desantis-new-legislative-proposal/</guid>
      <description>Governor Ron DeSantis of Florida has announced an extensive legislative proposal aimed at addressing illegal immigration threats in the state. The proposal seeks to address issues caused by the Biden administration&amp;rsquo;s failure to secure the US border. The legislation includes measures such as increasing penalties for human smuggling, strengthening detention statutes for illegal aliens, mandating the use of E-Verify, enhancing penalties for document falsification, and prohibiting local governments from issuing ID cards to people who are unlawfully in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consolidated Appropriations Act, 2023</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr2617/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr2617/</guid>
      <description>The bill being discussed is an appropriations bill that covers a range of policy areas and provides funding to federal agencies for the remainder of the fiscal year 2023. It includes the 12 regular appropriations bills that fund federal agencies, such as the Department of Defense, Department of Homeland Security, and Department of Labor, Health and Human Services, and Education. The bill also provides supplemental appropriations for disaster relief and to support Ukraine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Energy Cybersecurity University Leadership Act of 2023</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr302/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr302/</guid>
      <description>The Energy Cybersecurity University Leadership Act of 2023 is a bill that aims to support the development of a next-generation energy-specific cybersecurity workforce. The bill directs the Secretary of Energy to provide financial assistance to graduate students and postdoctoral researchers pursuing certain courses of study related to cybersecurity and energy infrastructure. The assistance will be provided on a competitive basis in the form of scholarships, fellowships, and research and development projects at institutions of higher education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Nikki Haley for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/nikki-haley-for-president-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/nikki-haley-for-president-2024/</guid>
      <description>Nikki Haley is an American politician, diplomat, and businesswoman. She was born on January 20, 1972, in Bamberg, South Carolina, and her birth name is Nimrata Nikki Randhawa. Haley is of Indian descent and is a member of the Republican Party.
Haley served as the 116th Governor of South Carolina from 2011 to 2017, becoming the first woman to hold the office in the state&amp;rsquo;s history. She was also the first Indian American woman to serve as a governor in the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Social Security Fairness Act of 2023</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr82/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr82/</guid>
      <description>H.R. 82 - Social Security Fairness Act of 2023
The &amp;ldquo;Social Security Fairness Act of 2023,&amp;rdquo; designated as H.R. 82 in the 118th Congress, was introduced on January 9, 2023, by Mr. Graves of Louisiana and co-sponsored by several other representatives. This bill aims to make significant changes to the Social Security system by addressing two key provisions: the Government Pension Offset (GPO) and the Windfall Elimination Provision (WEP). Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed breakdown of the bill&amp;rsquo;s provisions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Denouncing the horrors of socialism</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hconres9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hconres9/</guid>
      <description>The concurrent resolution denounces the horrors of socialism. The resolution states that socialist ideology results in the concentration of power which has frequently led to the establishment of communist regimes, totalitarian rule, and brutal dictatorships. The resolution highlights the fact that many of the worst crimes in history have been committed by socialist ideologues, including Vladimir Lenin, Joseph Stalin, Mao Zedong, Fidel Castro, and others. The resolution also mentions the devastating consequences of the implementation of socialism in various countries, such as the Bolshevik Revolution, the USSR gulags, the famine and devastation caused by the Great Leap Forward in China, the killing fields in Cambodia, and the current state of Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Chinese Surveillance Balloon Incident Sparks Condemnation</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hres104/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hres104/</guid>
      <description>This Resolution concerns a high-altitude surveillance balloon belonging to the People’s Republic of China (PRC) that was tracked by the Department of Defense over United States territory on February 2, 2023. It was later revealed that the balloon was first tracked by North American Aerospace Defense Command (NORAD) on January 28, 2023. The Secretary of Defense has stated that the balloon was being used by the PRC for surveillance of strategic sites in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Born-Alive Abortion Survivors Protection Act</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr26/</guid>
      <description>Born-Alive Abortion Survivors Protection Act This bill establishes requirements for the degree of care a health care practitioner must provide in the case of a child born alive following an abortion or attempted abortion.
Specifically, a health care practitioner who is present must
exercise the same degree of care as would reasonably be provided to any other child born alive at the same gestational age, and ensure the child is immediately admitted to a hospital.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> joe Biden for President 2024</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/joe-biden-for-president-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/joe-biden-for-president-2024/</guid>
      <description>Joe Biden is the 46th President of the United States, serving in office since January 20, 2021. Before becoming president, Biden was the Vice President of the United States under President Barack Obama from 2009-2017. Prior to that, Biden served 36 years as a senator from the state of Delaware.
Joe Biden priorities Controlling the spread of COVID-19 and accelerating vaccine distribution. Revitalizing the economy and promoting job growth. Combating climate change and transitioning to clean energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Guide for Homebuyers </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/articles/first-time-homebuyer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/articles/first-time-homebuyer/</guid>
      <description>Finding Your Perfect Home: A Guide for Homebuyers As a prospective homebuyer, finding your perfect home can be a daunting task. With so many options available, it can be challenging to know where to start. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a first-time homebuyer or a seasoned homeowner, this guide will provide you with the information you need to make an informed decision.
Understanding Your Needs and Wants Before you begin your home search, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand your needs and wants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Benefits of South Dakota Medicaid</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/articles/south-dakota-medicaid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/articles/south-dakota-medicaid/</guid>
      <description>Understanding the Benefits and Eligibility Criteria South Dakota Medicaid is a government-run health insurance program for low-income individuals and families. The program offers a range of health care services, including doctor visits, hospital stays, and prescription drugs, among others. In this article, we will take a deep dive into the benefits and eligibility criteria of South Dakota Medicaid.
Benefits of South Dakota Medicaid South Dakota Medicaid offers a wide range of health care services to eligible individuals and families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Role of Senators in Representing Constituents</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/articles/senators-roles-and-duties/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/articles/senators-roles-and-duties/</guid>
      <description>The Role of Senators in Representing Constituents As elected representatives of the people, senators play a crucial role in shaping the policies and laws that govern our nation. They are responsible for representing the interests and concerns of their constituents, and for advocating on their behalf in the legislative process. Whether you are looking to address a specific issue or simply want to stay informed about what is happening in your state or community, a senator can be a valuable resource and an effective advocate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is Medicaid?</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/articles/what-is-medicaid/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/articles/what-is-medicaid/</guid>
      <description>Everything You Need to Know Medicaid is a government-sponsored program that provides healthcare coverage for those who are financially eligible. It is a crucial safety net for millions of Americans, providing access to essential healthcare services and helping to reduce the financial burden of medical expenses. In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover everything you need to know about Medicaid, including eligibility requirements, covered services, and how to apply.
What is Medicaid?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guide to Contacting Your Senators</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/articles/how-to-contact-senators/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/articles/how-to-contact-senators/</guid>
      <description>A Comprehensive Guide to Contacting Your Senators As a citizen, it&amp;rsquo;s important to have a voice in government and make your opinions heard. One of the most effective ways to do so is by reaching out to your senators. In this guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover everything you need to know about how to contact your senators, including the best methods and what information to include.
Who are Your Senators? Before you can contact your senators, it&amp;rsquo;s important to know who they are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FairTax Act of 2023</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr25/</guid>
      <description>This bill imposes a national sales tax on the use or consumption in the United States of taxable property or services in lieu of the current income taxes, payroll taxes, and estate and gift taxes. The rate of the sales tax will be 23% in 2025, with adjustments to the rate in subsequent years. There are exemptions from the tax for used and intangible property; for property or services purchased for business, export, or investment purposes; and for state government functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>George Floyd Justice in Policing Act of 2021</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hr1280/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hr1280/</guid>
      <description>The bill under discussion aims to address a wide range of issues and policies related to policing practices and law enforcement accountability. It aims to increase accountability for law enforcement misconduct and enhance transparency and data collection. The bill also aims to establish best practices and training requirements for law enforcement officers.
One of the key provisions of the bill is to enhance existing enforcement mechanisms to remedy violations by law enforcement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> John Kennedy  for senator 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/john-kennedy-for-senator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2022 10:06:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/john-kennedy-for-senator/</guid>
      <description>A Little Bit About John Kennedy John Kennedy was elected to the U.S. Senate in 2016. Sen. Kennedy serves on the Appropriations, Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs, Budget, Judiciary and Small Business and Entrepreneurship committees in the U.S. Senate. He serves as the Ranking Member on the Subcommittee of Energy and Water Development for the Appropriations Committee, the Ranking Member on the Subcommittee of Federal Courts for the Judiciary Committee, and the Ranking Member on the Subcommittee of Economic Policy for the Banking Committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Laura Kelly for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/laura-kelly-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 13:02:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/laura-kelly-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Laura Kelly for Kansas governor Governor Laura Kelly has brought Democrats and Republicans together to balance the budget, fully fund our schools, and fight for a tax cut for all Kansans. Laura will always put what’s best for Kansas ahead of party politics.
Meet Laura Kelly Governor Laura Kelly brings together both parties to get things done for Kansas. Laura has brought jobs, businesses, opportunities, and record economic success to Kansas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Nellie Gorbea for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/nellie-gorbea-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 12:04:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/nellie-gorbea-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Nellie Gorbea for Rhode Island governor Rhode Island Secretary of State Nellie M. Gorbea was re-elected in 2018 to serve Rhode Island for a second term and continue making government work for people. She made history when she was sworn in on January 6, 2015, becoming the first Hispanic elected to statewide office in New England. Since then, she has rapidly emerged on the national scene as a leader who is taking on some of the toughest issues and getting results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tina Kotek for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/tina-kotek-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 12:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/tina-kotek-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Tina Kotek for Oregon governor Through my professional experience as an advocate for those in need, and serving in the State House where I’ve proudly led as Speaker, I have carried the value of service instilled in me by my parents to get real results for Oregonians.
My grandparents came from Eastern Europe in the early part of the last century to find opportunity and a better life. My parents were proud first-generation Americans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Michelle Lujan Grisham for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/michelle-lujan-grisham-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2022 11:06:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/michelle-lujan-grisham-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Michelle Lujan Grisham for New Mexico governor Michelle Lujan Grisham is the 32nd Governor of New Mexico and was the first Democratic Hispanic woman to serve as Governor of a U.S. state. As a 12th-generation New Mexican, she has dedicated her life to serving her community while fighting for families and building an economy that works for all New Mexicans.
After graduating from the University of New Mexico’s law school, Governor Lujan Grisham worked to provide free legal services for seniors with the state bar’s lawyer referral program for the elderly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Brenda Siegel  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/brenda-siegel-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:09:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/brenda-siegel-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Brenda Siegel for governor About Brenda Brenda was born in Brattleboro, Vermont. She graduated from Brattleboro Union High School and after college, she worked as a teacher, political intern, and choreographer. In 2002, she became a single mom and decided to open a small business and raise her child in Vermont near her own family. Brenda’s father was a commercial photographer and small business owner. Her mother was a dancer and is an American Sign language interpreter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Bob Stefanowski  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/bob-stefanowski-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/bob-stefanowski-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Bob Stefanowski for governor Bob Stefanowski grew up in a family like many of us are blessed to have.
His roots are on Dixwell Avenue in New Haven, where his family lived in a three-family home. Having his grandparents on the first floor meant lots of stories about how his family came to America through Ellis Island from Poland. Bob’s great grandmother shucked oysters in Fair Haven, he’s always been proud to have a family history in some of the world’s finest oysters!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tim Michels  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-michels-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Aug 2022 11:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-michels-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Tim Michels for governor Born and raised in Brownsville, Tim Michels, endorsed by President Trump, is a conservative outsider who has a plan to put Wisconsin on the right track.
At the age of nine, Tim’s dad handed him a shovel and taught him how to dig trenches, while his mom taught him how to drive trucks. After graduating from Lomira High School in Dodge County, he attended Saint Norbert College in Green Bay, where he was active in ROTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kari Lake  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kari-lake-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kari-lake-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kari Lake for governor Kari Lake, the former anchor for Fox 10 News in Phoenix, became a symbol of truth in journalism when she walked away from the mainstream media despite being number one in the ratings for more than two decades.
Now she&amp;rsquo;s running for Governor of Arizona on a platform of common sense conservatism dedicated to individual liberties, low taxes, limited regulation, and protecting Arizona&amp;rsquo;s great Western heritage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Katie Hobbs for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/katie-hobbs-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Aug 2022 11:08:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/katie-hobbs-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Katie Hobbs for governor Born and raised in the Grand Canyon State, Katie Hobbs has dedicated her life to listening to her community and helping solve difficult challenges for the people of Arizona. A fearless advocate for Arizona, Katie is ready to bring transparency and accountability to the Governor’s office and deliver real results for all of us.
Born and raised in Arizona, Katie learned the value of service at an early age from her parents and her church.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Chris Jones  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/chris-jones-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 11:07:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/chris-jones-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Chris Jones for governor As a son of two preachers, I was raised with a strong sense of faith. This faith has never collided with my love for science — in fact, it only made it grow stronger. I attended Morehouse College on a NASA Scholarship, for physics and math, then studied at MIT to become a nuclear engineer and earn a Ph.D. in urban planning. I was blessed to run the Arkansas Regional Innovation Hub, which provided the tools and technology Arkansans needed to build businesses and create jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Deidre DeJear  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/deidre-dejear-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 11:07:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/deidre-dejear-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Deidre DeJear for governor Iowans want someone to get to work for them. Deidre has dedicated her life to serving her community and that is what she will do as Governor starting on Day One.
Deidre was born in Jackson, Mississippi, and as a child moved with her family to Oklahoma. At eight years old, Deidre’s mother passed away shortly after giving birth to her younger sister. Overcoming this adversity at such a young age and seeing her dad be present for her and her siblings shaped who Deidre is today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kevin Stitt for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kevin-stitt-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Aug 2022 11:07:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kevin-stitt-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kevin Stitt for governor Governor Kevin Stitt is leading Oklahoma with a vision to become Top Ten in job growth, infrastructure, education and more.
Stitt is an entrepreneur who founded Gateway Mortgage in 2000 in Tulsa, Oklahoma. Starting with only $1,000 and a computer, he grew Gateway Mortgage into a nationwide mortgage company operating in more than 40 states and servicing more than $20 billion in residential mortgages.
In 2018, he led Gateway through a merger and established Gateway First Bank, which today is one of Oklahoma’s 10 largest banks with over $2 billion in assets, 160 mortgage centers across the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tim Scott  for senator 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-scott-for-senate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2022 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-scott-for-senate/</guid>
      <description>Tim Scott for senator Tim grew up in poverty in a single-parent household in North Charleston. His mom worked 16-hour days as a nursing assistant to keep food on the table and a roof over their heads. Tim admits his circumstances left him hopeless, and as a result, he nearly failed out of high school. By the grace of God, Tim met his mentor, a Chick-fil-A operator named John Moniz. Moniz taught Tim Biblical principles and Conservative values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Stacey Abrams  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/stacey-abrams-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:07:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/stacey-abrams-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Stacey Abrams for governor Stacey Abrams grew up in Gulfport, Mississippi, one of six children whose parents had three tenets: go to church, go to school, and take care of each other. Her father, a shipyard worker, and mother, a college librarian, faced financial hardships of their own, yet they taught their children the value of service to others. No matter how much they struggled to make ends meet, Stacey and her siblings were taught that someone always had less and that it was their job to serve that person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kay Ivey  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kay-ivey-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kay-ivey-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kay Ivey for governor When Kay Ivey was first sworn-in as the 54th Governor of the State of Alabama in April 2017, she got right to work cleaning up Montgomery and restoring the people’s trust in government. That’s because Kay is a conservative fighter, whose life has prepared her to lead our state towards prosperity and opportunity for every Alabamian.
She grew up working on the family farm in Wilcox County.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Maura Healey for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/maura-healey-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/maura-healey-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Maura Healey for governor Maura Healey has spent her career standing up for the people of Massachusetts and pursuing justice and equality. She’s running for Governor to bring people together and expand economic opportunities for everyone in Massachusetts.
Maura has deep roots in Massachusetts. Her parents both grew up in Newburyport. Her maternal grandparents met in Gloucester, where her grandfather worked on the fishing docks and her grandmother, whose ancestors settled on the Parker River in Newbury in 1636, went to nursing school.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Carol Blood for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/carol-blood-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/carol-blood-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Carol Blood for governor My name is Carol Blood. I’m a Nebraskan, born and raised. I was born in McCook, Nebraska, raised in rural Adams County, Nebraska and raised my family in Sarpy County, Nebraska. My husband Joe and I have been married for 34 years and are blessed with three adult children and 10 grandchildren.
I love my community and have been an active volunteer and community advocate for decades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kathy Hochul for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kathy-hochul-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:27 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kathy-hochul-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kathy Hochul for governor Kathy Hochul is the 57th Governor of New York. A lifelong New Yorker, she was born and raised in a blue-collar Irish Catholic family in Buffalo that instilled a deep passion for public service and activism. She continued that fighting spirit as a student organizer, as a young attorney and aide to Sen. Daniel Patrick Moynihan, and then as a member of her Town Board, Erie County Clerk, member of Congress, lieutenant governor, and now as governor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mark Gordon for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/mark-gordon-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 11:06:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/mark-gordon-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Mark Gordon for governor Mark Gordon was elected Wyoming’s 33rd Governor, on Nov. 6, 2018. He was sworn into office on January 7, 2019.
Mark Gordon grew up on the family ranch in Wyoming where he learned the values of hard work and integrity and the importance of working together. As Governor, he brings those values to the table, maintaining his commitment to a Wyoming where its citizens can pursue their dreams while the state retains its unique character.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Joe Lombardo  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/joe-lombardo-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:06:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/joe-lombardo-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Joe Lombardo for governor Joe is Running for Governor to Save Nevada
Joe Lombardo began his service to others in the United States Army and served bravely in the Army, National Guard, and Army Reserve - protecting Americans both domestically and abroad. After his service to his country, Joe dedicated himself to protecting our communities – serving in law enforcement over the last 30 years.
Joe quickly rose through the ranks of the Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department (LVMPD) and, after 26 years on the force, was elected as Sheriff of Clark County, Nevada in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mike DeWine  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/mike-dewine-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:03:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/mike-dewine-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Mike DeWine for governor Mike DeWine’s story is a true Ohio story. Growing up in Yellow Springs, Mike and Fran (Struewing) met in the first grade and married while students at Miami University. They’ve been blessed with eight children and 26 grandchildren. Family is at the core of everything Mike DeWine does, and that’s why he has devoted his life to fighting for Ohio’s families.
Guided by his family and faith, Mike has governed as a compassionate conservative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Nan Whaley  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/nan-whaley-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:03:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/nan-whaley-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Nan Whaley for governor Nan grew up in a small town in Indiana. She learned the values of hard work, strength, and resilience from her dad, a union autoworker who lost his job but never lost his dignity, and her mom, who went to work at the laundromat behind their house to help make ends meet.
Back then, Ohio was where people went for opportunity, so she attended the University of Dayton, becoming the first person in her family to graduate from college.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jamie Smith for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/jamie-smith-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:03:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/jamie-smith-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Jamie Smith for governor Jamie serves as Minority Leader in the South Dakota House of Representatives, where he has delivered bipartisan solutions for the people of South Dakota. Jamie believes we are strongest when we work together to get things done.
Jamie is a lifelong South Dakotan. A realtor and former educator, Jamie isn’t a career politician, and he understands the needs of all South Dakotans. Every day, Jamie rolls up his sleeves to bring people together on the big issues South Dakotans face: affordable housing, high-quality education and healthcare, and an economy that works for everyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kristi Noem for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/kristi-noem-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:41 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/kristi-noem-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Kristi Noem for South Dakota governor Kristi Noem is a wife, mother, grandmother, rancher, farmer, small business owner, and New York Times bestselling author of &amp;ldquo;Not My First Rodeo: Lessons from the Heartland.&amp;rdquo;
Governor Kristi Noem’s political career began with her 2006 election to the South Dakota State Legislature followed by her move to the United States House of Representatives and finally a return to Pierre as the state’s first female Governor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jared Polis for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/jared-polis-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/jared-polis-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Jared Polis for governor Governor Polis is a hard-working Coloradan who has run successful businesses, delivered better education opportunities for our kids and is now serving as Colorado’s 43rd Governor. Under his leadership, Colorado is working to become one of the most family-friendly states while topping the list of strongest state economies in the country.
Since taking office in 2019, Governor Polis has delivered on the top priorities he committed to tackle for Colordans – lowering the cost of childcare and getting more kids in free, full-day kindergarten, reducing the cost of healthcare, accelerating our fight against climate change and lowering taxes for hard-working families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gretchen Whitmer for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/gretchen-whitmer-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:36 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/gretchen-whitmer-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Gretchen Whitmer for governor Governor Gretchen Whitmer was inaugurated as the 49th governor of Michigan on January 1, 2019. Her career includes serving in the Michigan State House, as the first woman Senate Democratic Leader, and prosecutor for Ingham County, fighting for survivors’ rights and to reform how sexual assault cases are handled. Inspired by her service and family, she is dedicated to improving the lives of all Michiganders.
Gov. Whitmer has been a lifelong resident of Michigan, receiving both a BA and JD from Michigan State University.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Lou Leon Guerrero  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/lou-leon-guerrero-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:34 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/lou-leon-guerrero-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Lou Leon Guerrero for governor The Honorable Lourdes “Lou” Aflague Leon Guerrero is the ninth Governor of Guam. She is the first female governor of the territory and is a registered nurse, a businesswoman, a policymaker, a mother, and a grandmother.
Since taking office in January 2019, she’s nearly eliminated GovGuam’s deficit from $83 million to $1.5 million. Additionally, she increased the minimum wage, legalized cannabis, ended two federal receiverships, and paid millions in war reparations owed to Guam’s WWII survivors with adjudicated claims.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> les gara  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/les-gara-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/les-gara-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>les gara for governor Like many Alaskans, Les grew up without wealth or privilege. When he was six, a robber broke into his father’s office. He was working late and the robber killed him. Les grew up in foster homes, where he lived for twelve years until he graduated high school. While Les worked from grade school through law school, he had good public schools and the opportunity to succeed. That’s what everyone deserves: an equal right to opportunity, liberty and justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Albert Bryan  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/albert-bryan-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/albert-bryan-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Albert Bryan for governor Albert Bryan Jr. is the eldest son born to Albert and Genevieve (Pilgrim) Bryan. Born on February 21, 1968 on St. Thomas, U.S. Virgin Islands, he and his four brothers, Troy, Robert, Andre, and Alrick, lived with their parents in the historic St. Thomas neighborhood of Savan. When Governor Bryan was a teenager, Mr. Bryan, Sr. moved the family to St. Croix where he was offered a better career opportunity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Steve Sisolak  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/steve-sisolak-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/steve-sisolak-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Steve Sisolak for governor Steve Sisolak was born into a midwest working-class family. His parents Ed and Mary worked hard to provide for their three children and Steve inherited their blue-collar ethic, working full-time to put himself through college at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. Steve then enrolled in UNLV’s Graduate Studies Program, where he received a master’s degree in 1978.
Steve put down roots in Las Vegas, built his own communications business while raising his two daughters on his own as a single father.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> stephen heidt for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/stephen-heidt-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/stephen-heidt-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>stephen heidt for governor I&amp;rsquo;m not a career politician, but I know enough about right and wrong to make a difference in our great state.
EDUCATION AND LEADERSHIP As a 4th generation Idahoan who grew up in a small agricultural community a few miles south of Preston, Idaho. I had a modest upbringing and started working at the dairy down the street from my house at age 10. I was at work by 4:00 a.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Brad Little for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/brad-little-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:21 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/brad-little-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Brad Little for governor Brad Little is Idaho’s 33rd Governor, leading the people of Idaho through the most prosperous time in state history! A lifelong conservative, Governor Little’s first term is marked by historic tax relief, unparalleled red tape reduction, extraordinary economic growth, and unprecedented investments in education to ensure a strong workforce for years to come.
Governor Little is committed to continuing to lead Idaho with his goal for Idaho in mind – to make Idaho the place where we all can have the opportunity to thrive, where our children and grandchildren choose to stay, and for the ones who have left to choose to return.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Paul LePage for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/paul-lepaige-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/paul-lepaige-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Paul LePage for governor Paul was born and raised in Lewiston, Maine. The oldest son of eighteen children in an impoverished, dysfunctional family, Paul left home at the age of eleven to escape severe domestic violence.
He was homeless and living on the streets. He slept anywhere he could and earned as much as he could shining shoes and doing odd jobs. A Franco-American kid, a group then considered a minority in Maine and who had been aggressively targeted several years before in Maine by the Ku Klux Klan, life presented other problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Janet Trafton Mills for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/janet-mills-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/janet-mills-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Janet Trafton Mills for governor Janet Mills is Maine through and through – and no one loves this state or believes in its people more than she does. That’s why she has always fought for Maine people and always will. She wants to keep moving Maine forward.
Born and raised in rural Maine, Janet is the granddaughter of potato farmers from Aroostook County and the daughter of a World War II veteran and public school teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Is My Credit Score Calculated?</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/income/understanding-credit-scores/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/income/understanding-credit-scores/</guid>
      <description>A credit score helps lenders determine how likely you are to pay back what you owe. A good score can help you qualify for better interest rates on credit cards, car loans or a mortgage. Your credit score is based on factors that include payment history, your debt load and how long you’ve used credit. Reviewing your credit report regularly is the first step to improving your credit score. Having a good credit score is one of the keys to financial freedom.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gavin Newsom for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/gavin-newsom-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 12:06:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/gavin-newsom-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gavin Newsom for governor Gavin Christopher Newsom (born October 10, 1967) is an American politician and businessman serving as the 40th governor of California since January 2019. A member of the Democratic Party, he served as the 49th lieutenant governor of California from 2011 to 2019 and as the 42nd mayor of San Francisco from 2004 to 2011. Newsom attended Redwood High School and graduated from Santa Clara University. After graduation, he founded the PlumpJack wine store with family friend Gordon Getty as an investor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Brian dahle for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/brian-dahle-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:07:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/brian-dahle-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Brian dahlefor California governor Senator Brian Dahle is a voice for public safety, lowering taxes, and reducing homelessness. He opposes onerous government regulations that are driving up the cost of living forcing many to leave California and businesses to shutter their doors.
A longtime advocate of building a better business climate in California, Brian Dahle was the California Chamber of Commerce’s top-rated senator for pro-business votes in 2021 and has a 100 percent rating from the National Federation of Independent Business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Scott Jensen for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/scott-jensen-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:04:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/scott-jensen-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Scott Jensen for Minnesota governor Lifelong Minnesotan Born and raised in Sleepy Eye, Minnesota, Dr. Scott Jensen graduated valedictorian of his 1973 high school class. He attended the University of Minnesota obtaining an undergraduate degree in physiology, magna cum laude, and then attended Luther Theological Seminary seeking answers to life‘s biggest questions. The seminary proved to be an ideal setting for profound decision making as he made two life-changing decisions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tim Walz for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-walz-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-walz-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Tim Walzfor Minnesota governor Tim’s career has been defined by public service, from serving in the National Guard for 24 years, to serving our students as a high school teacher and football coach, to serving our state as a Congressman, and now as Minnesota’s 41st Governor.
Tim’s parents, Jim and Darlene, instilled in him the values that continue to guide his commitment to the common good and selfless service. Summers working on his family’s farm reinforced these lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Doug Mastriano for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/doug-mastrian-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/doug-mastrian-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Doug Mastrianofor Pennsylvania governor Doug Mastriano is a combat veteran and the son of a career US Navy man. He is an Eagle Scout and worked as a paperboy, janitor, security guard, short-order cook, pizza delivery person and dishwasher. Doug was commissioned in the U.S. Army in 1986 and served on the Iron Curtain with the 2nd Armored Cavalry Regiment in West Germany. While serving along the East German and Czechoslovakian borders, he witnessed the end of the Cold War and thereafter deployed to Iraq for Operation Desert Storm (1991) to liberate Kuwait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Josh Shapiro for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/josh-shapiro-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/josh-shapiro-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Josh Shapiro for governor Throughout his career as a public servant, Josh Shapiro has taken on the status quo, brought people together to solve tough problems, and delivered results for the people of Pennsylvania. Since 2017, he has served as the People’s Attorney General, working every day to stand up to powerful institutions and protect Pennsylvanians’ rights. Now, Josh is running to be Pennsylvania’s next Governor — to move our Commonwealth forward and tackle our biggest challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jason Martin  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/jason-martin-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/jason-martin-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Jason Martin for governor As a father, doctor, and business owner Jason Martin has dedicated his life to improving the lives and livelihoods of everyday Tennesseans.
Dr. Jason Martin was raised in Southern Alabama in a place much like many of our small communities in Tennessee. He was a latch key kid and his parents and step-parents worked hard every single day. While they labored hard to provide for Jason, his many aunts, uncles, and grandparents helped to raise him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Bill Lee for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/bill-lee-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/bill-lee-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Bill Lee for governor Bill Lee is a seventh-generation Tennessean who was raised in Franklin where he still resides today with his wife Maria on his family’s farm. He’s the proud father of four adult children (Jessica, twin sons Jacob and Caleb, and Sarah Kate) and nine grandchildren.
After attending Williamson County Schools, Bill went to Auburn University, where he studied Mechanical Engineering. When he graduated, he returned home to Franklin to join the family business his grandfather started in 1944.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Beto O’Rourke  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/beto-for-governor-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/beto-for-governor-2022/</guid>
      <description>Beto O’Rourke for governor Beto O’Rourke is a fourth-generation Texan, born and raised in El Paso where he has served as a small business owner, a city council representative and a member of Congress. He founded and currently leads Powered by People, a Texas-based organization that works to expand democracy and produce Democratic victories through voter registration and direct voter engagement. Powered by People has helped register over 250,000 unregistered Texans to vote since its inception in December 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Greg Abbott  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/greg-abbott-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/greg-abbott-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Greg Abbott for governor Named “Best Governor in the Nation” in his current second term, Governor Greg Abbott continues to build on his record as a strong conservative leader who fights to preserve Texas values and ensure the Lone Star State remains the best place to raise a family, build a business, and create greater opportunity for all.
Texas works when Texans work Under Governor Abbott’s strong stewardship, the Texas economy has expanded to nearly $2 trillion as the Lone Star State continues to break all records for total jobs, with more Texans working than at any point in the state’s history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ron DeSantis for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 10:05:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/ron-desantis-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Ron DeSantis is the 46th Governor of Florida.
A native Floridian with blue-collar roots, Ron attended Dunedin High School and worked his way through Yale University, where he graduated with honors and was the captain of the varsity baseball team. He also graduated with honors from Harvard Law School. While at Harvard, he earned a commission in the U.S. Navy as a JAG officer. During his active-duty service, Ron deployed to Iraq as an adviser to a U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contribution</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 10:02:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/donate/</guid>
      <description>Our mission at sengov.com is to bring transparency and accountability to the political landscape in our state. By creating a comprehensive directory of state representatives, we&#39;re making it easy for citizens to access important information and stay informed about the decisions being made on their behalf.
Running and maintaining sengov.com requires significant time and resources. We rely on the support of people like you to keep our website up-to-date and to provide the latest news, analysis, and resources for our community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>governor and senators Salaries and Benefits</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/salary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 10:02:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/salary/</guid>
      <description>governors Salaries and Benefits The average salary of a state governor in 2009 was $124,398. The highest salary currently being accepted is that of New York Governor Andrew Cuomo at $225,000. The lowest salaries are those of Maine Governor Janet Mills and of Puerto Rico Wanda Vázquez Garced at $70,000.
There have been several instances where the governor of a state has either refused their salary in its entirety or instead only taken $1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> About Monkeypox</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/articles/monkpoxy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/articles/monkpoxy/</guid>
      <description>About Monkeypox Monkeypox is a rare disease caused by infection with the monkeypox virus. Monkeypox virus is part of the same family of viruses as variola virus, the virus that causes smallpox. Monkeypox symptoms are similar to smallpox symptoms, but milder, and monkeypox is rarely fatal. Monkeypox is not related to chickenpox.
Monkeypox was discovered in 1958 when two outbreaks of a pox-like disease occurred in colonies of monkeys kept for research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Monkeypox Facts for People Who are Sexually Active</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/articles/monkeypox-facts-on-sexual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/articles/monkeypox-facts-on-sexual/</guid>
      <description>Monkeypox Facts for People Who are Sexually Active Monkeypox is a rare disease caused by the monkeypox virus. Monkeypox can cause a rash which may look like pimples or blisters, sometimes with a flu-like illness. Monkeypox can spread to anyone through close, personal, often skin-to-skin contact including:
Direct contact with monkeypox rash, scabs, or body fluids from a person with monkeypox. Touching objects, fabrics (clothing, bedding, or towels), and surfaces that have been used by someone with monkeypox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Monkeypox Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/articles/monkeypox-qa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/articles/monkeypox-qa/</guid>
      <description>What is monkeypox? Monkeypox is a rare disease caused by infection with the monkeypox virus. Monkeypox virus is part of the same family of viruses as variola virus, the virus that causes smallpox. Monkeypox symptoms are similar to smallpox symptoms, but milder, and monkeypox is rarely fatal.
Monkeypox was discovered in 1958 when two outbreaks of a pox-like disease occurred in colonies of monkeys kept for research. Despite being named “monkeypox,” the source of the disease remains unknown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment Eligibility and  Qualifying for Unemployment</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/eligibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/eligibility/</guid>
      <description>Am I Eligible? Your state determines your eligibility, how much you&amp;rsquo;ll receive, and how long you&amp;rsquo;ll receive it for. You can find information regarding your eligibility on your state&amp;rsquo;s official website.
To Qualify You lost your job through no fault of your own. Earned a certain amount of money during a &amp;ldquo;base period&amp;rdquo; of time prior to being let go. You are able to work and actively looking for a job to maintain eligibility.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>checkers</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/games/checkers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/games/checkers/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>chess</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/games/chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/games/chess/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>connect four</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/games/connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/games/connect/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>current U.S. senators</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/senate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/senate/</guid>
      <description> SH: Hart Senate Office Building SD: Dirksen Senate Office Building SR: Russell Senate Office Building </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>find me</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/games/findme/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/games/findme/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>games</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/games/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/games/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governors&#39; Powers &amp; Authority</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/power/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/power/</guid>
      <description>Overview Governors, all of whom are popularly elected, serve as the chief executive officers of the fifty states and five commonwealths and territories.
As state managers, governors are responsible for implementing state laws and overseeing the operation of the state executive branch. As state leaders, governors advance and pursue new and revised policies and programs using a variety of tools, among them executive orders, executive budgets, and legislative proposals and vetoes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Liquid Sort</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/games/liquid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/games/liquid/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>reversi</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/games/reversi/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/games/reversi/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>snake</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/games/snake/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/games/snake/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tic Tac</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/games/tictac/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/games/tictac/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senators Email Addresses</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/email/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/email/</guid>
      <description>Senator Email Addresses This is a list of email addresses for all current US Senators. Most senators provide an email form on their website rather than a direct email address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senators Mailing Addresses</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mail/</guid>
      <description>Senators Mailing Addresses This is a list of mailing/postal addresses for all current US Senators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Senators Phone Numbers</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/phone/</guid>
      <description>Senators Phone Numbers This is a list of phone numbers for all current US Senators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment Application</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/application/</guid>
      <description>When Should I File For Unemployment? You should file as soon as possible because it could take up to three weeks to begin receiving payments. The longer you take filing, the longer it will take to receive your first unemployment check.
How To Apply You can apply online, by mail or by phone. You should gather the necessary information, and get in contact with your state unemployment office to determine the best way to open a claim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unemployment Benefits</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/benefits/</guid>
      <description>Unemployment Benefits By State Every state has a maximum weekly wage that they distribute to eligible claimants. Some states will provide a weekly allowance for your dependents. The majority of states pay benefits at a maximum of 26 weeks with Massachusetts being the exception at 30 weeks, and Florida and North Carolina at 12 weeks.
The table below is there to give you an idea of the maximum unemployment benefits one could receive weekly, broken down by state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Applying for Food Stamps </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/snap/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/snap/</guid>
      <description>Applying For Food Stamps During COVID-19 States have changed the way they are processing Food Stamp applications during the coronavirus (COVID-19) emergency. Most, if not all, states have closed their offices to the public and are only taking applications online or by paper application received in the mail.
If you are unable to complete an application using either of these methods then contact your local Food Stamp office and ask what your rights are.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> IRS Stimulus Checks </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/income/stimulus-checks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/income/stimulus-checks/</guid>
      <description>Million of Americans received a first round of stimulus checks starting in April after the country shutdown and the economy took a hit. This guide will cover who qualifies for the first round of stimulus checks, who does not qualify for one, and any special requirements there may be in order to receive one.
Using the IRS Stimulus Check Portal The IRS Stimulus Check Portal is an online tool you can use to check on the status of your stimulus check, enter your direct deposit information, and confirm your mailing address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Senator Role to the people</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/income/senators-roles/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/income/senators-roles/</guid>
      <description>the majority of individuals don’t know the role their senators play in the senate. True, we tend to assume that the congressman’s mandate is to foresee projects in the government. However, what the majority don’t know is that every one of them has employees whose work is to deliver constituent service. The service is specially designed to help people with concrete issues- usually involving a federal agency.
In most cases, the senate works on sorting out issues around Internal Revenue Service problems, mortgage issues, social security problems, immigration requests, and veterans’ benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> contactgovernors is a privately operated website and is not part the United States Government and all information is based on public available information. use this form for site Inquiry only Email: Message: Send We do not represent any government entity. All information is based on public available information. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus Relief</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/income/covid-19-relief/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/income/covid-19-relief/</guid>
      <description>There are a number of programs available to Americans to help assist them throughout the coronavirus (COVID-19) pandemic.
Stimulus Checks &amp;amp; Financial Assistance Stimulus checks for American families Stimulus checks to help ease the economic strain caused by the coronavirus (COVID-19) crisis will be sent to the vast majority of Americans in the coming days and weeks. Most Americans will not need to do anything in order to receive their checks while some will be required to update their information before getting a check.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governors&#39; Office Functions</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Overview The structure and operation of governors’ offices vary across the states, commonwealths, and territories. Differences often reflect external factors such as the powers and authorities given to governors by constitution or statute as well as state tradition and custom. But possibly more important, they reflect and support each governor’s personal style.
Structure There are generally three basic models for the organization of a governor’s office:
Strict Hierarchy – All staff report to the governor through the chief of staff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
