<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tommy Tuberville on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tommy Tuberville on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 11:54:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Tuberville biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/bio/</guid>
      <description>who is Tommy Tuberville? EARLY LIFE Coach Tuberville was born in Camden, Arkansas on September 18, 1954, the third of three children of Olive and Charles Tuberville.
College Football&amp;rsquo;s 2004 Coach of the Year and two-time SEC Coach of the Year, Tommy Tuberville is most often recognized for his success on the field. But it is the legacy of his father, a highly decorated WWII veteran and Purple Heart recipient, that motivates Coach Tuberville to give back to the brave men and women of the United States Armed Forces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tommy Tuberville political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/political-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/tommy-tuberville/political-view/</guid>
      <description>SERVING THOSE WHO SERVED Changing The Way We Treat Our Veterans My father was a highly decorated WWII veteran and Purple Heart recipient, and that is why I am so passionate about changing the way our nation treats its Veterans. President Trump is off to a good start – Veteran unemployment is at its lowest point in history: 2.3%. But we can and must do more to help our Veterans re-enter the workforce and society.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
