<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Richard Shelby  on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Richard Shelby  on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Richard Shelby biograph </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/bio/</guid>
      <description>biograph Born in Birmingham, Alabama, Shelby received his law degree from the Birmingham School of Law in Birmingham, Alabama, in 1961. After law school in 1963, he went on to Senator Richard Shelby is the senior United States Senator from the State of Alabama. He was first elected to the U.S. Senate in 1986 and is currently in his sixth term.
Senator Shelby is the former chairman and current vice chair of the Senate Committee on Appropriations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Richard Shelby political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/political-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alabama/richard-shelby/political-views/</guid>
      <description>political Views Gun law Shelby has an A+ rating from the National Rifle Association for his support of gun rights. In 2016, Shelby voted against the Feinstein Amendment, which sought to stop the sale of firearms to people known or suspected to be terrorists. Upon being asked by Scott Wapner on why he voted against it, Shelby said &amp;ldquo;I do believe that we should keep guns out of the hands of terrorists, would-be terrorists, and a lot of other people.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
