<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kathy Hochul on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kathy Hochul on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kathy Hochul bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/bio/</guid>
      <description>know more about Kathy Hochul Kathy Hochul biograph Kathy Hochul is the 57th and first female Governor of New York State. Governor Kathy Hochul began her career in public service on her local Town Board before serving as Erie County Clerk, and then as a member of Congress for New York’s 26th Congressional District. She more recently served in statewide office as Lieutenant Governor and now as the first female Governor of the State of New York.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letitia James</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/james/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/james/</guid>
      <description>About the Attorney General Letitia James Letitia “Tish” James is the 67th Attorney General for the State of New York. With decades of work, she is an experienced attorney and public servant with a long record of accomplishments. She is the first woman of color to hold statewide office in New York and the first woman to be elected Attorney General.
In 2013, Ms. James was elected Public Advocate for the City of New York and became the first woman of color to hold citywide office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Rodriguez </title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/robert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/new-york/kathy-hochul/robert/</guid>
      <description>About the Secretary of State Robert Rodriguez Robert J. Rodriguez is currently serving as the Secretary of State. He was nominated by Governor Kathy Hochul to serve as New York’s 68th Secretary of State.
Mr. Rodriguez is a uniquely accomplished leader and former legislator, with civic and legislative successes that have been focused strategically on investing in and developing public-good infrastructure projects, creating good-paying jobs and addressing financial disparities for historically underrepresented minorities and low-income communities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
