<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Maine on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/categories/maine/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Maine on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/categories/maine/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Paul LePage for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/paul-lepaige-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/paul-lepaige-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Paul LePage for governor Paul was born and raised in Lewiston, Maine. The oldest son of eighteen children in an impoverished, dysfunctional family, Paul left home at the age of eleven to escape severe domestic violence.
He was homeless and living on the streets. He slept anywhere he could and earned as much as he could shining shoes and doing odd jobs. A Franco-American kid, a group then considered a minority in Maine and who had been aggressively targeted several years before in Maine by the Ku Klux Klan, life presented other problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Janet Trafton Mills for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/janet-mills-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/janet-mills-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Janet Trafton Mills for governor Janet Mills is Maine through and through – and no one loves this state or believes in its people more than she does. That’s why she has always fought for Maine people and always will. She wants to keep moving Maine forward.
Born and raised in rural Maine, Janet is the granddaughter of potato farmers from Aroostook County and the daughter of a World War II veteran and public school teacher.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
