<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ohio on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/categories/ohio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ohio on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:03:46 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/categories/ohio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Mike DeWine  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/mike-dewine-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:03:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/mike-dewine-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Mike DeWine for governor Mike DeWine’s story is a true Ohio story. Growing up in Yellow Springs, Mike and Fran (Struewing) met in the first grade and married while students at Miami University. They’ve been blessed with eight children and 26 grandchildren. Family is at the core of everything Mike DeWine does, and that’s why he has devoted his life to fighting for Ohio’s families.
Guided by his family and faith, Mike has governed as a compassionate conservative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Nan Whaley  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/nan-whaley-for-gov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:03:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/nan-whaley-for-gov/</guid>
      <description>Nan Whaley for governor Nan grew up in a small town in Indiana. She learned the values of hard work, strength, and resilience from her dad, a union autoworker who lost his job but never lost his dignity, and her mom, who went to work at the laundromat behind their house to help make ends meet.
Back then, Ohio was where people went for opportunity, so she attended the University of Dayton, becoming the first person in her family to graduate from college.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
