<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RESOLUTION on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/categories/resolution/</link>
    <description>Recent content in RESOLUTION on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/categories/resolution/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Denouncing the horrors of socialism</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hconres9/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hconres9/</guid>
      <description>The concurrent resolution denounces the horrors of socialism. The resolution states that socialist ideology results in the concentration of power which has frequently led to the establishment of communist regimes, totalitarian rule, and brutal dictatorships. The resolution highlights the fact that many of the worst crimes in history have been committed by socialist ideologues, including Vladimir Lenin, Joseph Stalin, Mao Zedong, Fidel Castro, and others. The resolution also mentions the devastating consequences of the implementation of socialism in various countries, such as the Bolshevik Revolution, the USSR gulags, the famine and devastation caused by the Great Leap Forward in China, the killing fields in Cambodia, and the current state of Venezuela.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Chinese Surveillance Balloon Incident Sparks Condemnation</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/bills/hres104/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/bills/hres104/</guid>
      <description>This Resolution concerns a high-altitude surveillance balloon belonging to the People’s Republic of China (PRC) that was tracked by the Department of Defense over United States territory on February 2, 2023. It was later revealed that the balloon was first tracked by North American Aerospace Defense Command (NORAD) on January 28, 2023. The Secretary of Defense has stated that the balloon was being used by the PRC for surveillance of strategic sites in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
