<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lisa Murkowski on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lisa Murkowski on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Murkowski biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/bio/</guid>
      <description>senator Dan Sullivan biograph Lisa Murkowski, Alaska’s senior U.S. Senator, is a third generation Alaskan proudly serving as the first Alaskan born senator. Murkowski was born in Ketchikan and raised in towns across the state, including Wrangell, Juneau, Fairbanks, and Anchorage. She is married to Verne Martell and they have two grown sons. Lisa loves spending time in the Alaska outdoors. She’s an avid skier, has hiked on glaciers, enjoys fall duck hunts, and has a pretty impressive King Salmon mounted on her office wall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lisa Murkowski Political Views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alaska/lisa-murkowski/political/</guid>
      <description>Political Views Senator Lisa Murkowski is a moderate Republican. Since winning re-election in 2010, her voting record has been deemed by some as &amp;ldquo;more moderate&amp;rdquo; when compared to her previous years in the Senate. The National Journal, in 2013, gave Murkowski a composite score of 56% conservative and 45% liberal. The National Journal ranked her as the 56th most liberal and 44th most conservative member of the Senate. CrowdPac, which rates politicians based on donations they receive and give, has given Murkowski a score of 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
