<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Private on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/private/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Private on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/military/usmc/private/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Private First Class</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/pfc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/pfc/</guid>
      <description>Private First Class is the second-lowest rank in the Marine Corps, ranking above Private and below Lance Corporal. A Private First Class in the Marines is equivalent in paygrade to a Private (PV2) in the Army, and is a full paygrade lower then an Army Private First Class because the Marine Corps only has one Private paygrade instead of the Army&amp;rsquo;s two.
The rank of Private First Class was introduced by the Marine Corps following service in WWI in 1917 to mirror the Army&amp;rsquo;s rank structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lance Corporal</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/lcpl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/lcpl/</guid>
      <description>Lance Corporal is the third enlisted rank in the Marine Corps, equivalent to a Private First Class in the Army. Unlike the rank of Corporal, a Lance Corporal is not considered a non-commissioned officer. However, Marines promoted to this rank are expected to show a degree of leadership and skill in serving as role models for newly enlisted recruits.
While the Army temporarily had Lance Corporals in the 1960s, the Marine Corps is currently the only branch of the armed forces that maintains this rank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Corporal</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/cpl/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/cpl/</guid>
      <description>A Corporal in the Marine Corps is a junior noncommissioned officer, and is equivalent in rank to the Army&amp;rsquo;s junior NCO ranks of Corporal and Specialist. Corporals usually command small contingents of Marines in combat and operations, including four-man fireteams (which may also be lead by a Lance Corporal) or eight-man squads comprising of two fireteams.
The Marine Corps specializes in small-unit operations, and as a result Corporals hold a significant amount of authority and resposibility in contrast to the lighter duties of Lance Corporals and Privates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgt/</guid>
      <description>Sergeant is a junior noncommissioned officer rank in the USMC, and the oldest rank in the Marine Corps. Sergeants serve as squad leaders in combat operations, and lead a squad of eight soldiers including one or more Corporals.
Because the Marine Corps operates many missions on the fireteam and squad level, Marine Corps sergeants often have a great deal of leadership and responsibility in carrying out their objectives.
Because of their expanded role in direct combat oparations, promotion to sergeant is handled on a case-by-case basis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staff Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/ssgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/ssgt/</guid>
      <description>Staff Sergeant is the first of the staff non-commissioned officer ranks in the United States Marine Corps. Generally experienced Marines with 10 to 13 years of service, Staff Sergeants most often serve as a platoon sergeant for a platoon consisting of 30 or more Marines.
As a platoon sergeant, Staff Sergeants may act as the top tactical advisor to their platoon commander during combat and support operations. In day-to-day deployment and training, a staff sergeant will also assist with training and administrative operation of his platoon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gunnery Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/gysgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/gysgt/</guid>
      <description>A Gunnery Sergeant in the United States Marine Corps is a specialized non-commissioned officer who manages firepower and logistics for a company-sized unit of Marines.
The rank of Gunnery Sergeant is unique to the Marine Corps, and was introduced in the 19th century. While serving aboard Navy vessels, Marine contingents were expected to help man the ship&amp;rsquo;s weapons in gun crews of four to five marines. The leader of each gun crew was a specialized Marine who trained his gun crew in firing procedure, ammunition handling, and other essential skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/msgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/msgt/</guid>
      <description>First Sergeant is a senior non-commissioned officer&amp;rsquo;s rank in the United States Marine Corps. A First Sergeant shares the E-8 paygrade with Master Sergeant, although the two ranks have separate spheres of responsibility.
A First Sergeant serves as the senior enlisted advisor to the commander of a medium-to-large unit of Marines, such as a platoon or a company. As the senior enlisted advisor, First Sergeants hold the responsiobility of being the main bridge between enlisted Marines and their company commander.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/1stsgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/1stsgt/</guid>
      <description>First Sergeant is a senior non-commissioned officer&amp;rsquo;s rank in the United States Marine Corps. A First Sergeant shares the E-8 paygrade with Master Sergeant, although the two ranks have separate spheres of responsibility.
A First Sergeant serves as the senior enlisted advisor to the commander of a medium-to-large unit of Marines, such as a platoon or a company. As the senior enlisted advisor, First Sergeants hold the responsiobility of being the main bridge between enlisted Marines and their company commander.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Master Gunnery Sergeant</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/mgysgt/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/mgysgt/</guid>
      <description>Sergeant Major is the highest enlisted rank in the Marine Corps, and is equivalent in paygrade (but not in responsibility) to Master Gunnery Sergeant.
A Sergeant Major serves as the billeted senior enlisted advisor for the Marine Corps&amp;rsquo; largest units, including battalions and squadrons. As the senior enlisted member of their unit, Sergeant Majors serve as a bridge between the enlisted Marines and their commanders and assist in unit logistics, drilling, and disciplinary actions among their Marines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sergeant Major</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgtmaj/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgtmaj/</guid>
      <description>Sergeant Major is the highest enlisted rank in the Marine Corps, and is equivalent in paygrade (but not in responsibility) to Master Gunnery Sergeant.
A Sergeant Major serves as the billeted senior enlisted advisor for the Marine Corps&amp;rsquo; largest units, including battalions and squadrons. As the senior enlisted member of their unit, Sergeant Majors serve as a bridge between the enlisted Marines and their commanders and assist in unit logistics, drilling, and disciplinary actions among their Marines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sergeant Major Of The Marine Corps</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgtmajmc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/military/usmc/sgtmajmc/</guid>
      <description>Sergeant Major is the highest enlisted rank in the Marine Corps, and is equivalent in paygrade (but not in responsibility) to Master Gunnery Sergeant.
A Sergeant Major serves as the billeted senior enlisted advisor for the Marine Corps&amp;rsquo; largest units, including battalions and squadrons. As the senior enlisted member of their unit, Sergeant Majors serve as a bridge between the enlisted Marines and their commanders and assist in unit logistics, drilling, and disciplinary actions among their Marines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
