<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nevada on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/categories/nevada/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nevada on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:06:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/categories/nevada/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Joe Lombardo  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/joe-lombardo-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:06:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/joe-lombardo-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Joe Lombardo for governor Joe is Running for Governor to Save Nevada
Joe Lombardo began his service to others in the United States Army and served bravely in the Army, National Guard, and Army Reserve - protecting Americans both domestically and abroad. After his service to his country, Joe dedicated himself to protecting our communities – serving in law enforcement over the last 30 years.
Joe quickly rose through the ranks of the Las Vegas Metropolitan Police Department (LVMPD) and, after 26 years on the force, was elected as Sheriff of Clark County, Nevada in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Steve Sisolak  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/steve-sisolak-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2022 10:02:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/steve-sisolak-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Steve Sisolak for governor Steve Sisolak was born into a midwest working-class family. His parents Ed and Mary worked hard to provide for their three children and Steve inherited their blue-collar ethic, working full-time to put himself through college at the University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee. Steve then enrolled in UNLV’s Graduate Studies Program, where he received a master’s degree in 1978.
Steve put down roots in Las Vegas, built his own communications business while raising his two daughters on his own as a single father.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
