<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pennsylvania on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/categories/pennsylvania/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pennsylvania on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:03:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/categories/pennsylvania/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Doug Mastriano for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/doug-mastrian-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/doug-mastrian-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Doug Mastrianofor Pennsylvania governor Doug Mastriano is a combat veteran and the son of a career US Navy man. He is an Eagle Scout and worked as a paperboy, janitor, security guard, short-order cook, pizza delivery person and dishwasher. Doug was commissioned in the U.S. Army in 1986 and served on the Iron Curtain with the 2nd Armored Cavalry Regiment in West Germany. While serving along the East German and Czechoslovakian borders, he witnessed the end of the Cold War and thereafter deployed to Iraq for Operation Desert Storm (1991) to liberate Kuwait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Josh Shapiro for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/josh-shapiro-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 11:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/josh-shapiro-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Josh Shapiro for governor Throughout his career as a public servant, Josh Shapiro has taken on the status quo, brought people together to solve tough problems, and delivered results for the people of Pennsylvania. Since 2017, he has served as the People’s Attorney General, working every day to stand up to powerful institutions and protect Pennsylvanians’ rights. Now, Josh is running to be Pennsylvania’s next Governor — to move our Commonwealth forward and tackle our biggest challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
