<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roger Wicker  on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Roger Wicker  on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Roger Wicker biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/bio/</guid>
      <description>who is Roger F. Wicker ? Roger F. Wicker has represented Mississippi in the United States Senate since December 2007. During his time in the Senate, Wicker has championed pro-growth policies to create jobs, limit federal overreach, protect life, and maintain a strong national defense.
Wicker is the ranking member of the Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation for the 117th Congress. He served as chairman of the full committee during the 116th Congress after previously serving as the chairman of the Senate Commerce Subcommittee on Communications, Technology, Innovation, and the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roger Wicker political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/politic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mississippi/roger-wicker/politic/</guid>
      <description>Senator Roger Wicker Bio Roger Frederick Wicker is a senior American attorney and politician. He was born on July 5, 1951, in Pontotoc, Mississippi. He is currently serving as the senior U.S Senator from Mississippi for the last fifteen years.
A member of the Republican Party, Wicker previously served as a member of the United States House of Representatives and the Mississippi State Senate. He has worked as an officer in the U.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
