<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dan Sullivan on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dan Sullivan on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Know more about Dan Sullivan biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/bio/</guid>
      <description>Who is senator Dan Sullivan? Senator Dan Sullivan represents Senate District 21, which includes parts of Craighead County and Jonesboro. He was elected to the Senate in November of 2020 and was sworn in on the first day of the regular session of 2021.
Senator Sullivan is a member of the Senate Committee on City, County and Local Affairs Committee and the Senate Public Health, Welfare and Labor Committee. He is also a member of the Legislative Joint Auditing Committee and the Joint Performance Review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dan Sullivan Political Views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/alaska/dan-sullivan/political/</guid>
      <description>Political Views Abortion / LGBT Sullivan opposes abortion, except in cases of rape, incest, or threat to the life of the mother; he also has voiced his opposition to same-sex marriage.
Healthcare He opposes the Affordable Care Act and believes it should be repealed and replaced.
Undocumented Immigrants &amp;amp; Energy Sullivan is against granting amnesty for undocumented immigrants, and is a proponent of an &amp;ldquo;all-of-the-above&amp;rdquo; energy policy, including increased drilling for oil.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
