<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tennessee on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/categories/tennessee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tennessee on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:02:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/categories/tennessee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Jason Martin  for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/jason-martin-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 11:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/jason-martin-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Jason Martin for governor As a father, doctor, and business owner Jason Martin has dedicated his life to improving the lives and livelihoods of everyday Tennesseans.
Dr. Jason Martin was raised in Southern Alabama in a place much like many of our small communities in Tennessee. He was a latch key kid and his parents and step-parents worked hard every single day. While they labored hard to provide for Jason, his many aunts, uncles, and grandparents helped to raise him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Bill Lee for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/bill-lee-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 10:02:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/bill-lee-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Bill Lee for governor Bill Lee is a seventh-generation Tennessean who was raised in Franklin where he still resides today with his wife Maria on his family’s farm. He’s the proud father of four adult children (Jessica, twin sons Jacob and Caleb, and Sarah Kate) and nine grandchildren.
After attending Williamson County Schools, Bill went to Auburn University, where he studied Mechanical Engineering. When he graduated, he returned home to Franklin to join the family business his grandfather started in 1944.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
