<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>contact mike dewine email on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/tags/contact-mike-dewine-email/</link>
    <description>Recent content in contact mike dewine email on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/tags/contact-mike-dewine-email/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mike DeWine</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/ohio/mike-dewine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/ohio/mike-dewine/</guid>
      <description>Governor Mike DeWine Mike DeWine’s story is a true Ohio story. Raised in Yellow Springs, Ohio, Mike DeWine and Fran (Struewing) met in the first grade and married while students at Miami University. They’ve been blessed with eight children and 26 grandchildren. Family is at the core of everything Mike DeWine does, and that’s why he has devoted his life to fighting for Ohio’s families. He knows when families are strong, Ohio communities are stronger, and our future is bright.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mike DeWine bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/ohio/mike-dewine/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/ohio/mike-dewine/bio/</guid>
      <description>know more about Governor Mike DeWine Mike DeWine’s story is a true Ohio story. Raised in Yellow Springs, Ohio, Mike DeWine and Fran Struewing met in the first grade and married while students at Miami University. They’ve been blessed with eight children and 26 grandchildren. Family is at the core of everything Mike DeWine does, and that’s why he has devoted his life to fighting for Ohio’s families. He knows when families are strong, Ohio communities are stronger, and our future is bright.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
