<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Minnesota on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/categories/minnesota/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Minnesota on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:04:20 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/categories/minnesota/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Scott Jensen for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/scott-jensen-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:04:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/scott-jensen-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Scott Jensen for Minnesota governor Lifelong Minnesotan Born and raised in Sleepy Eye, Minnesota, Dr. Scott Jensen graduated valedictorian of his 1973 high school class. He attended the University of Minnesota obtaining an undergraduate degree in physiology, magna cum laude, and then attended Luther Theological Seminary seeking answers to life‘s biggest questions. The seminary proved to be an ideal setting for profound decision making as he made two life-changing decisions:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tim Walz for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-walz-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:03:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/tim-walz-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Tim Walzfor Minnesota governor Tim’s career has been defined by public service, from serving in the National Guard for 24 years, to serving our students as a high school teacher and football coach, to serving our state as a Congressman, and now as Minnesota’s 41st Governor.
Tim’s parents, Jim and Darlene, instilled in him the values that continue to guide his commitment to the common good and selfless service. Summers working on his family’s farm reinforced these lessons.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
