<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kyrsten Sinema on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kyrsten Sinema on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:54:12 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kyrsten Sinema biograph</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/bio/</guid>
      <description>who is senator Kyrsten Sinema Kyrsten knows firsthand the challenges everyday Arizonans face. Born in Tucson, Kyrsten went through some tough times growing up. Her family struggled to make ends meet, and for a while they were even homeless. But they got by thanks to family, church, and hard work. Kyrsten’s childhood experience showed her the power of hard work and the importance of helping others.
Education was Kyrsten’s ticket to a better life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyrsten Sinema Political Views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/political/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/political/</guid>
      <description>Political Views Sinema has been described as a centrist or moderate Democrat. According to National Journal&amp;rsquo;s 2013 Vote Ratings, her votes place her near the center of their liberal-conservative scale. The National Journal gave her a composite ideology score of 57% liberal and 43% conservative. According to the Bipartisan Index created by The Lugar Center and the McCourt School of Public Policy, Sinema was the sixth most bipartisan member of the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kyrsten Sinema campaign manifest</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/campaign/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Oct 2021 11:54:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/arizona/kyrsten-sinema/campaign/</guid>
      <description>FIXING A DYSFUNCTIONAL WASHINGTON Arizonans know Washington is dysfunctional. Too many politicians are more concerned about the next election than doing what’s best for everyday people. Many think the rules we all follow don’t apply to them.
Not Kyrsten.
Kyrsten was ranked the third most independent member of Congress. Kyrsten supports the No Budget, No Pay bill that says if Congress doesn’t pass a budget, they shouldn’t get paid. She voted against her own pay raise and cosponsored legislation to dock pay for members of Congress who engage in bad behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
