<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tate Reeves on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tate Reeves on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tate Reeves bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/bio/</guid>
      <description>know more About Governor Tate Reeves As the 65th Governor of Mississippi, Tate Reeves continues to build on his strong record as a conservative leader who fights to guard taxpayers’ dollars, improve educational opportunity, and grow new careers so that our state’s best and brightest can raise their families and thrive here at home.
In his inaugural address, Governor Reeves promised that this would be an administration for all Mississippi. He committed to a mission to create a climate where good careers are plentiful with every Mississippian prepared to pursue them, as he has every single day of his time serving our state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>spouse</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/spouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/mississippi/tate-reeves/spouse/</guid>
      <description>know more About First Lady of Mississippi Elee Williams Reeves First Lady of Mississippi, Elee Williams Reeves, grew up in Tylertown where her parents emphasized the importance of education and giving back to the community.
After graduating from McComb High School, she pursued her degree at Millsaps College in Jackson, graduating with honors. Elee also holds a Master’s degree in Business Administration from Millsaps College.
Beginning her career in 2001, Elee helps others reach their financial goals as an investment advisor with Coker &amp;amp; Palmer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
