<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jay Inslee on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jay Inslee on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Denny Heck</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/denny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/denny/</guid>
      <description>About Lieutenant Governor Denny Heck Denny Heck is humbled to serve as Washington’s 17th Lieutenant Governor. First elected in 2020, Lieutenant Governor Heck brings to the office a lifetime of experience in the public, private, and non-profit sectors.
As Lieutenant Governor, he is the President of the Washington State Senate and Chair of the Senate Rules Committee. He also serves as Acting Governor whenever Governor Inslee is out of the state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bob Ferguson</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/bob/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/bob/</guid>
      <description>About Washington State Attorney General Bob Ferguson Bob Ferguson is Washington State’s 18th Attorney General. As the state’s chief legal officer, Bob is committed to protecting the people of Washington against powerful interests that don’t play by the rules. He is a fourth-generation Washingtonian, a graduate of the University of Washington and New York University law school. Bob and his wife, Colleen, are the proud parents of 14-year-old twins, Jack and Katie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Hobbs</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/hobbs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2021 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/washington/jay-inslee/hobbs/</guid>
      <description>About Secretary of State Steve Hobbs Steve Hobbs is Washington’s 16th Secretary of State. He was appointed by Gov. Jay Inslee to replace Kim Wyman, who resigned mid-term to join the Department of Homeland Security’s Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA). Secretary Hobbs began his tenure Nov. 22, 2021.
As head of one of the most diverse offices in state government, Secretary Hobbs is responsible for managing state and local elections, corporation and charity filings, Washington State Library, Washington Talking Book &amp;amp; Braille Library, and Washington State Archives.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
