<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tina Smith  on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tina Smith  on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Tina Smith bio</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/bio/</guid>
      <description>I have been honored to serve as your Senator since January 2018 and I’m proud of the work we’ve done together since then. I moved to Minnesota the summer of 1984 with my new husband Archie. My first job in Minnesota was at General Mills. Archie and I moved to St. Louis Park, had our two sons Sam and Mason (who are now married!), and found our life in Minnesota. A few years later I started my own business, and at the same time got more active in my community volunteering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tina Smith political views</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/politics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 11:48:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/minnesota/tina-smith/politics/</guid>
      <description>Senator Tina Smith Bio Christine Elizabeth Smith is a former businesswoman and an American politician. She is currently serving in Minnesota as a Junior U.S. Senator since 2018. She is currently a member of the DFL Minnesota.
Senator Tina Smith was born on March 4th, 1958 in New Mexico. She was raised in Santa Fe. She attended Manderfield and Acequia Elementary. She completed her high school in Northern California.
After high school, she went to Stanford and completed her Bachelor’s degree in Political Science from there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
