<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>California on Contact United States Senators and Governors</title>
    <link>https://sengov.com/categories/california/</link>
    <description>Recent content in California on Contact United States Senators and Governors</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sengov.com/categories/california/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative David A. Alvarez</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/david-alvarez/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/david-alvarez/</guid>
      <description>Assemblymember David Alvarez was elected to the California State Assembly in June of 2022 to represent the 80th Assembly District in San Diego County.
Assemblymember Alvarez is a small business owner and has served for fifteen years in government, including eight years as a San Diego City Councilmember. A proud advocate of the underserved in San Diego, his previous successes included building parks, libraries and fire stations in neighborhoods that did not have them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Rebecca Bauer-Kahan</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/rebecca-bauer-kahan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/rebecca-bauer-kahan/</guid>
      <description>Assemblymember Rebecca Bauer-Kahan was first elected to represent Assembly District 16 in the California State Assembly in 2018, which includes Alamo, Danville, Dublin, Lafayette, Livermore, Moraga, Orinda, Pleasanton, San Ramon, and Walnut Creek.
Rebecca is an accomplished attorney, environmental advocate, community volunteer, law professor, and mother. A Bay Area native, she is the granddaughter of refugees who came to the United States to escape the Holocaust. Their experiences inspired her to use her career and personal time to help others in her community, solve complex problems, protect civil rights, and fight to ensure everyone has the opportunity to succeed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Steve Bennett</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/steve-bennett/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/steve-bennett/</guid>
      <description>Assemblymember Steve Bennett was elected to the Assembly in November 2020 and represents the 38th district that includes the western part of Ventura County.
Born and raised in the Midwest, Steve developed a strong sense of community responsibility. After graduating from Brown University with an Honors Degree in Economics, Steve served his community as a high school Economics and American History teacher for over 20 years. At the same time, he advanced solutions to community problems of urban sprawl, money corrupting politics, and problems encountered by disadvantaged communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Jasmeet Bains</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/jasmeet-bains/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/jasmeet-bains/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Jasmeet Bains Sworn in as Assemblymember for District 35
Assemblymember Dr. Jasmeet Bains was elected to the California State Assembly in November of 2022 to represent the 35th Assembly District.
Assemblymember Bains worked as a family doctor providing primary healthcare to families throughout the Valley. Dr. Bains also serves as a volunteer with Global Family, an organization dedicated to combating human trafficking and child abuse, on the San Joaquin Valley Air District’s Environmental Justice Advisory group, working to improve our Valley’s air and water quality and on the Taft College Foundation, fighting to expand access to higher education.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Joaquin Arambula</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/joaquin-arambula/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/joaquin-arambula/</guid>
      <description>Dr. Joaquin Arambula was elected in 2016 to represent the 31st Assembly District in Fresno County in the Central Valley. He is the first Latino physician elected to the California State Assembly.
He proudly represents a district that includes a majority of the City of Fresno, the rural cities of Fowler, Sanger, Selma, Orange Cove, and Parlier and unincorporated communities in southern and eastern portions of Fresno County.
Arambula’s experience as an emergency room doctor in Selma forged his determination to improve health care for all people, especially the most vulnerable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Cecilia M. Aguiar-Curry</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/aguiar-curry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/aguiar-curry/</guid>
      <description>In November 2016, Cecilia Aguiar-Curry was elected to the California Assembly to represent the 4th District that includes all or parts of Napa, Lake, Yolo, Sonoma, Colusa and Solano counties.
Cecilia grew up in western Yolo County and has long served her community. After going to school and working in the Bay Area for several years, she moved back to her hometown of Winters where she almost immediately became active in the local community and a regional leader on several issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Dawn Addis</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/dawn-addis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/dawn-addis/</guid>
      <description>Dawn Addis was elected to the California State Assembly in 2022 to represent the 30th Assembly District. Dawn is a special education teacher who began teaching in public schools over 20 years ago, and holds a Master of Arts (MA) degree in special education from San Francisco State University.
She has teaching credentials in elementary education, secondary education and special education and is fluent in Spanish. Dawn&amp;rsquo;s long record of community involvement includes co-founding the Women&amp;rsquo;s March in San Luis Obispo and being a Planned Parenthood Central Coast Action Fund board member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact representative Juan  Alanis</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/state/juanalanis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 May 2023 10:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/state/juanalanis/</guid>
      <description>Juan Alanis began a career in public service on his 21st birthday when he proudly pinned on a badge as a law enforcement officer. For nearly three decades, he has dedicated his life to protecting others. Juan has received three awards for saving the lives of others, including a decoration for rescuing a child whose father was trying to burn down a house with his daughter inside it.
The newly created 22nd Assembly District is more than just borders on a map; for Juan, it is home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gavin Newsom for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/gavin-newsom-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 12:06:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/gavin-newsom-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Gavin Newsom for governor Gavin Christopher Newsom (born October 10, 1967) is an American politician and businessman serving as the 40th governor of California since January 2019. A member of the Democratic Party, he served as the 49th lieutenant governor of California from 2011 to 2019 and as the 42nd mayor of San Francisco from 2004 to 2011. Newsom attended Redwood High School and graduated from Santa Clara University. After graduation, he founded the PlumpJack wine store with family friend Gordon Getty as an investor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Brian dahle for governor 2022</title>
      <link>https://sengov.com/candidates/brian-dahle-for-gov-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2022 11:07:20 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sengov.com/candidates/brian-dahle-for-gov-2022/</guid>
      <description>Brian dahlefor California governor Senator Brian Dahle is a voice for public safety, lowering taxes, and reducing homelessness. He opposes onerous government regulations that are driving up the cost of living forcing many to leave California and businesses to shutter their doors.
A longtime advocate of building a better business climate in California, Brian Dahle was the California Chamber of Commerce’s top-rated senator for pro-business votes in 2021 and has a 100 percent rating from the National Federation of Independent Business.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
